We are doing a just chatting slashreact
day today. We got a lot of videos we're
going to be watching, a lot of products
that we're going to be potentially
ordering chat because we're going to be
doing the first part of a two-part Etsy
series. So, uh, if you've been in my,
you know, chat for a while, you know
that time and time again, I'll do
product reviews where you guys send in
suggestions and then I go through, well,
okay, see how here's how it works. You
guys send in suggestions. You send in
5,000 suggestions.
98% of them are absolute dog. My lovely
mods, Wods, sift through that and
suggest the products that they think
would be funny, fun, stupid, scary, blah
blah blah to review. I get like 50 from
them. I might add like five, 10 myself.
And then we go through those and pick
like 20 uh to like 25 that we order. And
then when they come in, we do the second
part, review it, piece those two
together, bang, YouTube video. We've
done it with Amazon, we've done it with
Teimu, and today we're going to be doing
it with Etsy. Uh, so we're going to be
going over, I think, like around 50 Etsy
products. Uh, and normally we would go
through all of them and then we have
like a straw poll where you guys vote
for like what best 10 you like and then
we just take the top 20 and do it. I
kind of hated that process because it's
like you're just gonna [\h__\h] forget
what products you enjoyed. So, I think
instead we're just going to do we go
over the 50 and every single one we're
not going to do a poll, but you guys are
just going to type, you know, yes or no.
Yes meaning buy, no meaning don't buy.
And then, you know, we'll mark down
which ones we get. We'll have a maximum
of like 25 soft 25. You know, if we want
to order more, we could order more. If
not, we uh don't. And then the only
other rule is I get three, count them,
three vetos. I'm allowed to say no to
three products that chat says yes to.
Okay? Cuz some of the things that you
guys suggest are, you know, really
stupid or annoying or lame. That's lame.
That's not lame. It's fair. Chat, I give
myself three vetos as a safety net. I
only end up really using like one, maybe
two. Dildos. My mods didn't include the
dildos. Those are just null and void.
We're not actually going to be going
over those today. Are we ready, chat? We
have 40 voice crack. We have 48 products
to go through on Etsy. When I tell you I
thought about trashing this idea. I had
done Amazon. I had done Teeu. I went
Etsy, that's cool. Oh, [\h__\h] Everything
is literally like custommade products.
So it's like these are it's not weird.
It's just like you'll see. You'll see.
You'll see. First item lock in. I get
three vetos. Remember you type yes or no
if you want me to order it. But keep in
mind we have a 25 item cap soft cap. So
if you say yes for the first 25 items,
then we're [\h__\h] for the last one. So
you know it's a bit of gambling. It's a
bit of a It's a bit of deal or no deal
type situation here. Sh for the sub.
Editor, can we uh blur this? Uh Bart
mooning the camera. Thank you. Um see
off rip. I'm noticing the price tag.
Chat, you're not you're not losing your
mind. You did not just have a stroke.
That is actually $256.95.
And the product is 19 cm wide and 29 cm
tall. How many How many inches is 29
centimeters? Cuz I feel like $200 for a
product that's about yay big. That's
pretty ass.
It has a fivestar review. So I don't
know who the [\h__\h] would buy this chat.
This is a waste of money. Who would pay
that amount of money for this? This
seems ass. Also, I kind of assumed that
Bart Simpson was a bit of a shark type
creature where he has a cartilage in his
body rather than bones. You know, I feel
like if you were to punch Bart Simpson
in the face, it would recoil
kind of like a squishy slime figurine.
I didn't assume that he had a skull.
Okay, one in chat if we buy, two for no.
That's what we'll do cuz the yes and nos
I'm not I'm not vibing with. I'm seeing
more twos than ones. I agree. I'm happy
that chat is locked and dialed in right
now because this is a terrible product.
I I don't know who suggested this. I
know it's part of the meme because you
know Joe Bart Bart Bart Simpson ass. Who
the hell would spend that amount of
money on that? I would have been pissed
if you guys voted yes. Thank [\h__\h] Thank
[\h__\h] Let's delete that from the dock.
Okay, there we go. Next. See, now this
is what I'm talking about, chat. This is
This next product is something uh that
Etsy connoisseurs could get behind. Uh a
taxiderermy rat with a monle and a top
hat sitting on a stool. So, a dead mouse
stuffed and holding a teacup uh having
some sort of tea party. Some would say
$80. But I let me tell you, chat, tax
probably a pretty tough career. Uh oh my
god. Hold up. A dapple little rat named
Lord Squeak cheese.
He's ready to move into a new home and
bring an air of elegance and refinement.
This is a pre-order. The rat may vary in
color. They kill the rat if I order
this. Or do you think they just have a
bunch of dead skinned rats on standby
and they're going to stuff them? Due to
this being a pre-order, rat fur color
might not be the same as the picture.
I've also had to switch the chairs I use
so they're a bit different than
pictured. This will not ship before
Christmas. Takes two to three weeks.
Yeah, he's got to go out and find the
rat. He looks like a distinguished fine
gentleman. I I agree. I think this is a
yes. Okay, so we're going to write down
yes for the taxiderermy rat sitting on a
chair with a monle and a pipe. Next
product.
Not bad. Not great. Excited to see what
chat thinks.
a strawberry milkshake scented candle in
the shape of a strawberry milkshake. I
think this thing is most definitely a
fire hazard. [music] Uh, I think Candle
Wishes is probably making these straight
out of their home and I think this might
be a little scary to leave unattended.
Uh, because I'm curious how the wax
melts in this middle figure part here.
Is it edible? I don't know, but I would
want to take a bite of it to find out.
I'm going to go with no. But it is a soy
candle and you can't eat soy. This is
getting a lot of twos. Chat's voting no
for the soy candle. Not shocking at all.
We delete that. Strawberry milkshake out
of the books. Next one. I know this is
going to be a yes from chat. I don't
even really need to show you guys, but I
know you guys are going to want to see
it. An authentic Captain America shield.
I mean, that looks actually pristine. Oh
my god.
shiny aluminum. When I tell you I feel
like you could you could throw this
thing like a Frisbee. And it comes with
a strap. Is that just a trash can lid?
Is that Is that Is that just a Is that a
Is that a deformed trash can lid? No.
No. It looks harder. Who cares?
Whatever. It's Captain America shield.
It comes in different sizing options. I
would probably get the biggest one.
$300.
Holy.
Could I settle for the 24 in? Why is 6
in another $140?
What the [\h__\h] 24. 24. That's [\h__\h]
nuts, chat. That's [\h__\h] nuts. That's
average. You got to go big or go home. I
don't know. 30 in. 30 in for another
[\h__\h] $150. It's handmade. Yeah, but
do you think he's like bending the metal
himself?
I wonder how that works. Do we settle
for the third? Do we settle for the 24
or get the 30? See, here's Oh my god,
it's on sale. It's 30% off. It's
normally $425.
Do you think that's a scam? And they're
just saying it's on sale. So, it's sale,
so it seems cheaper. 24 or 30. Okay.
Well, you guys are obviously going to
vote 30. It's not your money.
All right, I'll write it. I'll write it
down. Wait, hold up. Let me edit it. 30
inch
30 inch. Pause. 30 inch shield. You're
rich, Joe. Yeah, but what the [\h__\h] am I
going to do with the shield after the
video? I could be Captain America next
year for Halloween.
Cinema. Cinema. I cosplay as Captain
America. Oh, cinema. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. No. Yeah. We're getting
that. Okay. I'm not upset anymore.
$300 purchase in the in the [\h__\h]
books. I didn't really set a price limit
for this one, but I do have three vetos.
So, if we see something that's like too
expensive, I'll just remove it. Is this
a fur? Not a fursuit, but it is a
ear and tail combo. Husky ear and tail
set. Shepherd dog ear cosplay set for
conventions and Halloween. Is that
authentic fur?
pass. We're getting a mixture here. Can
we get a poll? Can we get a poll going?
Right now, we've p I think we've passed
on two and said yes to two. Okay, you
can't have the third option on the poll
be Joe's bald because now we're having
inaccurate poll ratings. Can we get a
Can we get a repole? Cuz 21% of the
votes were Joe's bald. 56 55% yes.
Barely on the yes right now. Okay, lock
back in here, chat. Next one. See, I
don't know. This is too much of Marvel.
H. We'll see. What do you guys think? It
is a uh wearable tactical
black. Is this Black Panther? It says
bat helmet, but this looks just like
Black Panther, right? I think that's
like a copyright thing where they might
not be able to say Black Panther. It
kind of looks low quality if I'm being
honest. Oh, that's Batman. This looks
like Black Panther. That does not look
like Bat Oh, it is Batman. That looks
like Black Panther's mask, though,
doesn't it? In Marvel Rivals with the
ears. That's Batman, you [\h__\h] idiot.
Okay. Why are you getting that angry
that I mistakenly said that this was
Black Panther? I think this is kind of
lame. Your head's too big for it. All
right. Why are we just making fun of me
right now? Can we stay on? I don't like
this. I feel like this is going to be
like a shitty mesh helmet that you spend
like $80 on and they give you like a
scrape like it looks like it's a worn
down like batarang but it's just going
to be like a flimsy like aluminum
batarang. All right, this one got voted
no. Your forehead's too big. Yeah, I
wouldn't fit in the helmet. I would wear
it and the eye holes would be up here
because it doesn't it doesn't conform to
my head.
Tactical bat helmet out of the books.
Next one. This see this is just slop.
What are these [\h__\h] products?
What are these [\h__\h] products? Danny
De Cheeto
fridge magnet. It is a 3D printed
fridge. Hilarious Danny Devito Cheeto
mashup. Oh, it's so funny. Wow.
$6.
It's an easy purchase. It's a stupid
purchase, but it's an easy purchase. Six
bucks. Okay, we get it. Next. Oh, I love
these because they're always so cringy.
They're always the worst products.
Okay, the [\h__\h] insult
insult card deck. Insult a week for a
year. Contains 52 cards featuring some
of the most creatively offensive insults
money can buy you. If you're going to be
two-faced, at least make one of them
good-looking.
That is not
the most creatively infensive offensive
insult money could buy. I think Chat GPT
could come up with better insults.
Another example here. Don't worry, the
first 30 years of childhood are always
the hardest. Why? Why is there a
quantity button? Who's ordering more
than one of these?
Chat, this is a sleeper pick. I think we
get this one. That's lame. I don't give
a [\h__\h] I'm getting it. I'm also allowed
to buy a product if I want to. There's
an unlimited purchase amount from me.
You guys have a cap. I'm allowed to say
yes if I want to say yes. So, I'm going
to get that. It doesn't count on the 25
limit. Okay. We're getting the insult
cards because it'll be funny. I'll And
then I'll I'll use them when people are
mean to me in Marvel Rivals. Somebody's
like, "Dude, you're [\h__\h] terrible." I
go, "Oh, yeah.
I I bet your mother hates you.
Oh, yeah. I Oh, wow. Being 25 and still
living with your parents is so cool.
Oh, yeah. And then I pull out another
card. That's [\h__\h] cinema, chat. We're
getting that. It was only like eight
bucks. What a [\h__\h] steal. I I wonder
what the texture of this thing is. The
allseeing brain. Oh god, it comes with
an eyelash. Does it move?
No. That's That's so bad. That is so
bad.
Oh my god. Is it wet?
It's $44. Oh, you pick the eye color.
Blue, brown, green, or red.
I feel like the red one's the creepiest.
But the blue one looks the most
realistic. The red one doesn't look like
an actual eye. People voted yes. What
color do we get? Blue. The blue one
looks the most real. Like it has the
texture to the eye. The other ones just
kind of look like solid.
I'll write down blue. Official official
IMDb top 100 movie scratchoff poster.
Gift for movie lovers film fans. Premium
art print. So it just it's just a list.
What do you scratch off? It's just Do
you Oh, do you scratch them off as you
watch them? Like you've seen If you've
seen them, that means you you scratch it
off. Kind of like how you put like a
sticker for national parks on like a
water bottle.
I mean, that's not that bad, but who's
going to the IMDb top? Do you guys do
that when you want to find a movie you
want to watch is you just look at the
IMDb top 100? I mean, if you're like a
big movie connoisseur that's kind of
chill, but this is like useless for like
stream unboxing.
Like, what the hell am I gonna do? Yeah,
there's no content there. I agree. We're
skipping that. Oh, see now this is
this is content. Thick Pokemon, gold
metal card, funny stocking stuffers.
A threeack of thick Charizard, thick
Pikachu, and thick Blastoise. Booty Clap
and Thunder Cheeks. Does that say power
bottom? Oh, soggy bottom.
Hydro Hands. This attack does 40 damage
plus 10 more damage for each energy
attached to thick Blastoise.
Do you think these are like usable cards
in Pokemon play? I haven't played
Pokemon TCG in, you know, maybe 15 years
over that. I was probably like 10 when I
last played Pokemon. These look
valuable. I got some sleeves, too. I
could put them in.
Full set of threes. $18.99. That's not
bad.
We'll get those as well. Okay, so right
now we have one, two, three, four, five,
six products. Oh god, we have like 30
more to go through. More than that. Holy
[\h__\h] Okay, this is going to be we I
feel like we got to crank through these.
Next one. Bat signal mini spotlight.
Y'all are voting yes on this.
What am I going to do with this? What am
I going to [\h__\h] do with this chat?
This is a $65 product. I'm going to put
it up. I'm going to shine the bat
signal. Okay. Yeah, maybe if I had
gotten the mask. See? Oh, [\h__\h] See
though, then it would have been a good
pairing. If we had gotten the mask, if
we had gotten the mask, it would have
been good. Now you have to get the mask.
But the mask isn't going to fit me. Oh,
you guys voted 55% no. Yeah, it would
have been it could have worked as a
pairing, but as a single thing, it's
useless. Okay, this is just stupid. I
already feel my lungs hurting at this
pipe glass hot dog bowl. I'm inhaling
lead if I smoke out of this. Tobacco use
only. I'm saying right now I'm not
smoking tobacco out of that. [laughter]
If I get that product, the last thing
that would be I would smoke crack out of
that before I smoke tobacco out of a
[\h__\h] bowl. You're kidding me. You
will? I don't think I've ever bought
tobacco. I bought cigars, dude. People
that buy loose tobacco. If you buy loose
tobacco, you're over the age of 55.
I don't know anybody that's like a
millennial that would buy that. All
right. Yeah, I know chat's going to vote
yes for that. All right. Next. I'm such
a fat [\h__\h] chud t-shirt.
Self-deprecating humor gift. Funny,
sarcastic quote. Now, this is clearly AI
on this like woman with four dream
catchers behind her. I mean, how many
dreams are we having? Uh I I feel like
this woman in the photo is probably the
last person that would buy and wear I'm
such a fat [\h__\h] Chud shirt. The lady
would not be wearing that. That's what
I'm saying. You need to get like a gamer
wearing this. Some guy some guy that's
like I don't know maybe doom queuing
like a Val lobby. Wow, they come in so
many different colors.
Yeah, she's wearing like short jean
shorts.
Stake. Stake is the epitome of the guy
that would wear I'm such a fat [\h__\h]
Chud shirt. Exactly. Stake the YouTuber.
I feel like I should gift this to him.
Should I buy two and ask to ship him
one? All right, we'll get one. I don't
know what color to do. Probably black.
All right, NEXT. OH, NO. OH, WAIT. NO, I
have the backup on this one. I was going
to say this one's sold out. Okay, wait.
I'm going to show you guys what you guys
suggested and then what I found as a
backup. I didn't really review most of
these. I just ended up looking at them
to see if they were like sold out. This
is what you guys sent. It is a $60
Spongebob magic conchk shell with like
preloaded words and [\h__\h] and you could
like pull the string and it'll play
stuff to you. They don't have anymore.
So, I found one that is of much lesser
quality but is surely cinema. Mystic
conchell version 4 plus 90 plus lines
noncanon parody of Magic Conchell. Kind
of looks um like it was 3D printed.
and maybe that the rip cord would break
if you pulled it. Uh, the mayor of
stupid town called, "It's for you." A
lot of funny quips from the magic
conchk. Should I eat this super
delicious burger? No. Mystical conchk.
Will I get ever get married? Maybe
someday.
At least if I [laughter] buy this, my
wife will love me again. What?
What? Without the mystic conchk, I would
have never cured my depression. Dude,
who is selling this? Money grubbers.
Without the mystic conchk, I would have
never cured my depression. Oh, it comes
in so many different colorways.
Isn't the OG purple? Why would I want it
to look like Ratatouille? That looks
terrible. We have to get that. I feel
like that'll be [\h__\h] hilarious. What
do you think it's gonna say on it? All
right, next. This is an interesting I
don't even know how this I don't
understand how this product works if I'm
being honest. Like when I saw this one,
I kind of read into it and I uh because
it's not really a product. It's uh a $7
moth card from Bart Coppins.
So, this guy Bart Coppins will handdraw
me
an image of a moth for $7
personal mail and then he'll send you a
bunch of images of moths. Who is he?
He's Bart Coppins. Receiving Here's a
review, Chad.
Receiving this handwritten note from
Bart felt like opening a message from
the heart of the forest itself. Every
word carried warmth and passion. You
could feel his love for butterflies in
the wild places they come from. It's
rare these days to find somebody who
pours such authenticity into their work.
The little note is now treasure, a
reminder that beauty still arrives in
the simplest, most human ways. Thank
you, Bart, for sharing your art and your
journey. I think I have to get it. Bro,
look at this guy cooking up a [\h__\h]
moth a moth image by the fireplace like
with seven different flower vases right
next to him.
Thank you, Bart. All right, this one's
straight ass.
Cocktail recipe drink cards with
bartender gift sets.
It's just a bunch of playing cards. Like
a 52 playing card deck, but every card
is a different cocktail.
That's [\h__\h] stupid.
No, I don't even care. Okay, I'm glad
chat said no, cuz I was going to say I'm
vetoing that. Can we stop with the spicy
[\h__\h] every single review? Okay, it's
like
I do the one chip challenge, I do it
again, then we have the Amazon review
and people are like, "Oh, buy the
world's hottest chocolate." We have the
Teeu one. I buy some other weird [\h__\h]
Like, what is with what is with just
going, "Oh, let me just make Joe buy a
[\h__\h] Carolina Reaper." What is this
seasoning? They're vials.
Most organic Trinidad scorpion powder,
ghost pepper powder, habanero powder,
Carolina Reaper.
I would eat a little bit of this. I
don't think it would be that bad if I
had like maybe a finger of like powder,
but I'm not about to eat the whole vial.
Is that drugs? No, it's just like
[\h__\h] I think it's just literally
ground up Carolina like dried Carolina
Reaper. Why are people selling food on
Etsy?
Should we talk about that? Why are you
selling Why are you selling edible
products on Etsy? It's content. Yeah,
it's content. Snort it. Yeah, that'd be
great. I go to the [\h__\h] hospital. All
right. So, the Carolina Reaper is a yes.
Next one. A replica of a Call of Duty
Black Ops Ray Gun.
I believe this is the Is this Ray Gun
Mark 1? Yeah.
Or Mark 2? Oh, well, now I just put us
in a bit of a conundrum because you guys
are going to answer my question by
typing the number when the number is
also supposed to say what what version
this is. It's Mark One. Okay. Oh my god.
Does it open too? Does it shoot? Is
there a video of it working or is it
just on display? Oh, and it's the
mystery box under it.
I just hope it's not 3D print, bro. See,
it's plastic. It's going to come in,
dude. It's [\h__\h] 3D printed, bro.
Like, for $142.
It does glow, though. So, he's putting
some sort of [\h__\h] electronics in it.
I don't like when it's made from
plastic, though. Whenever Whenever
there's an Etsy product made of plastic,
I assume that they're just [\h__\h] 3D
printing it. Why does he have a glove
on? I can tell you right now, this guy
has hairy knuckles. Look at his
forearms. Not judging.
Just saying. It's in 20 people's
baskets. This is probably like the
ultimate girlfriend to boyfriend gift.
Am I wrong? You have a boyfriend that
loves Call of Duty. There's 20 There's
20 people that have this in their cart
for their boyfriend's birthday cuz they
know they love Call of Duty Black Ops
zombies. Great item. Guests loved it.
Guests loved it. What do you mean guests
loved it? It's a great conversation
piece. If somebody says that they're an
NPC, I'm saying, "All right, we'll get
the [\h__\h] $142 ray gun." If somebody
says something is a good conversation
piece, they are a [\h__\h] NPC. Okay. You
need to buy a $200 Etsy product to
[\h__\h] put it on a table to be like,
"Why don't we spark a conversation about
that?" No, you just have it. A 67 fidget
spinner 3D printed as like every other
product on Etsy is for some [\h__\h]
reason. Oh, you get a two pack. What a
steal. Do you think the ball bearings on
it are a gun? I don't even know what I
just said there. Good. It does kind of
look mesmerizing. Ooh, we have a bit of
an even even in odds here, chat. We got
to start saying no to some things. I
think we've said no. I think we said yes
to the last like six products. Right
now, we have 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 selected and we have like 25 more to
go through. If we're going to say no,
this might be one to say no to. It is
only [\h__\h] $9,
so I could buy it for the memes. We'll
put it on back roll. Maybe we could
cycle back to it.
It's probably a no. Next. One piece
anime press on nails. I could do them at
the start to stream and then do this. I
love with when people with nails do
this.
You know what I'm talking about? It
makes that
Are you able to get pressed on nails off
easily or are they like if they're on
for like a month, I probably don't want
them. These are like hand painted too.
This is awesome. Straw hat crew. There's
a shape and size. What size nail do you
think I am?
The options are small, extra small,
small, medium, large, and custom. I'm
assuming I'd be large. The biggest
option. Large. And then shape is almond
or coffin. For the people that know what
the [\h__\h] that means. Do we have any
[laughter]
Do we Do we know what the [\h__\h] that
means? Almond, I'm assuming, is in the
shape of an almond. How do you make a
nail in the shape of a coffin? See this,
bro? I don't know if I want to veto
this. I don't know if I want to veto
this one. I just don't really trust
buying this off of Etsy, if I'm being
honest. I know it's a trusted seller
platform, but I don't think I want to
buy custom golden grills from [\h__\h]
Etsy. Like, I know it only says $90
right now, but if you get a full set,
it's $1,600.
It's a [laughter] thous,00.
They have to send me a mold that I have
to send back and then they would make
them. I don't have to buy a full piece.
Like, I could buy
If I only bought a two-piece top,
that would be 90 bucks.
But the problem with that then is it's
just the [\h__\h] two front teeth. Like
that's stupid. I think it would be funny
to get grills for content, but I think I
would rather actually get them from like
a place that genuinely
makes grills in person, not like a
random seller on Etsy. Grills Factory87.
expert crafted premium 14 karat gold.
Like I'm not trusting an Etsy seller to
give me 14 karat gold.
[laughter]
Like I genuinely think I'm going to get
sent some boof [\h__\h] I'm vetoing that.
I'm not buying gold grills on Etsy.
That is a pass, bro. See, can we stop
with this [\h__\h] dude? Like what the
[\h__\h] are we to
hot sauce making DIY? So, it's not even
a hot sauce. I'm not even buying hot
sauce. I'm buying a kit to make hot
sauce. Like, you don't You get all the
ingredients.
You get habanero peppers and then the
spice blends and yours. My mouth's kind
of watering at this.
I am a little hungry. Trust me, it's
good. What are we thinking here? 55% no.
All right, we pass. Next. Dwayne Johnson
fidget slug
3D printed. You need this. Why are you
typing that in all caps?
You need this.
Yes.
Yeah. Yeah. You need a Yeah, you need to
buy that. You need to buy Yeah. Okay.
Another taxiderermy rat. This one's
holding a Corona extra or vodka.
And they're smiling.
mounting mechanism. What the [\h__\h] does
that mean? These look [\h__\h] Dude,
these look dehydrated.
Don't those look kind of scary?
It's 5:00 somewhere. Smiley face. God,
this is like a fever dream. What's the
warning? This product contains a small
magnet. Swallowed magnets can stick
together across intestines. All right,
I'm saying right now that is uh natural
selection. If you eat a magnet out of a
dead rat, okay, if you There's no need
for the warning. I understand the
legality there, but if you eat the dead
rat, if you eat the taxiderermy rat and
die, that's on you. Okay, I'm going to
say that right now. This This is not
like something like a tide pod that
looks like candy to a toddler. Like, if
you're eating the [\h__\h] taxiderermy
rat, you're stupid. Like that's that's
[\h__\h] nuts. Oh, with magnets sold out.
We only can get the without magnet.
Okay, so we could eat the dead rat when
it comes in. A medieval Gambison brown
legging Viking costume. I feel like this
is kind of lame if I don't have a full
Well, it does come with a full set. Does
it come with the pads? Does it come with
the the shoulder guards and [\h__\h] Like
if it's just this Oh, no. It does come
with it. Okay. How's it Does it
I kind of need the whole fit. Okay. I
hope it doesn't say medieval costume. Do
you think it says medieval costume on
it? Oh, no. That's just a watermark.
Yeah, cuz I'm really going to steal this
and re-upload it.
Okay. It comes with all the straps and
everything. That's good. Oh god, they
have like nine different sizes. All
right, people are voting yes. Oh my god,
we need to start I Okay, we might have
to cycle back and cut [\h__\h] out. But I'm
not going to lie, cuz right now we have
1 2 3 4 5 6 Wait. Yeah. 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15 16 17 18 19 already. And we
have 20 more.
No, we have 15 more to go through.
Circumcision survivor shirt.
I'm tired of making these [\h__\h] ass
polls. I'm sorry, mods.
54% yes. How many did I use a veto yet?
No. This is a waste of a veto. This is a
waste of a veto. I used one. Okay, so I
have two more. We'll buy that. Fine.
Jukebox Bluetooth speaker made with real
wood. This is a replica of the Minecraft
speaker or Minecraft jukebox. But I
don't know if the discs it seems like
it's just a speaker in a box. Do you do
you think the the discs actually play
the the Minecraft songs associated with
them? Short press, backtrack, long
press,
skip track, USB, USB input. So, it's
just a speaker.
It's just a speaker. All right, people
are voting yes on that as well. Jesus
Christ. We're at 20 items now. All
right, next. I'm voting no. I'm vetoing
this. I'm vetoing this and I can't wait
to veto this because I don't give a [\h__\h]
if it looks cool. The goo lamp candle
glow goo white steel tea light lamp.
It's a [\h__\h] lava lamp that is lit by
a [\h__\h] candle.
No, that's stupid.
And it's $150.
Why would I buy that? I have a threeft
lava lamp behind me. Granted, it takes
two hours to warm up. Valid complaint,
but it's still a sick ass lava lamp. And
that one th this is like the same price
as the lava lamp I bought. And I have to
use a [\h__\h] candle. No. And that [\h__\h]
Yo, that [\h__\h] is actually going to
explode. I'm vetoing that. The goo lamp
is a no foot candle.
You have no more vetos. I have one more
veto. I do have one more veto. if need
be. What do you think it smells like?
Foot. It's not worth the veto. It's not
worth the veto. I agree. If people vote
for it, it's easier to veto the more
expensive [\h__\h] Like I I'm not going to
veto an $11 foot candle. I'll just buy
it. Or a $13 foot candle. I'll just buy
it. But I'm going to veto the stupid
lava lamp. We said no to the grills, but
I didn't veto the grill. Maybe that
counts as a veto. No, I get one more
veto and I'm using it on the next one.
Uh,
>> I know I'm using it on the next one
because you unless you guys vote yeah or
unless you guys vote no. A one to one
scale chainsaw man helmet. While cool, I
don't watch the anime and I have no
[\h__\h] reason to buy this [\h__\h] This is
stupid. Not for people that like the
show. This is a cool product, but I've
never seen Chainsaw Man. I Why Why would
I own a $250 one to one replica for a
anime that I don't watch? Thank [\h__\h]
Chat voted no. I get one more veto. It's
peak. I don't care. I haven't seen it.
Will I watch it at some point? Maybe.
Can we do another wave? We'll do yes,
no, yes, no. We're going to have to go
back and cut out like five, six
products. Is that fine? Because you guys
are saying yes to like three out of
every four. And I know. Looking at the
next ones, I feel like all of these are
just going to be yeses. Gloving.
LED gloves. We would do We would do a
gloving show. 55% yes. I would do a
whole thing like the where they go.
Okay. Wait. No. I don't want to start
making weird things with my hands. That
could be uh misconstrued for something
else. Um. Yeah. Okay. So, yes on yes on
the on the gloves. Next, a dried
dandelion nightlight. Cool. Not good.
Chat, you guys for future, you guys got
to send [\h__\h] that's like not just cool,
like something that's cool to review.
What the [\h__\h] am I going to say about
this? It's a cool product, but I'm like
I'm going to I'm going to plug it in and
then and then I'm just going to go um
it's a dandelion light. It's dandelion
light. All right. Yeah, 98%. Now, see,
this is just stupid. Wait, actually, I
thought this was just like a cigarette
box. Retro cigarette box bubble toy set.
3D printed fidget with two wand sticks
and refillable tube. So, it's a
cigarette box that you blow bubbles out
of 3D printed cigarette sticks and
bubble solution. Why is this $53?
And who's buying this? Like, I get that.
I would I feel like everybody that has
there's four people that have this in
their cart. I feel like four people that
have this in their cart have to be
YouTubers, bro. Because like who's
going, "Oh, I really want to buy the
bubble cat [\h__\h] uh fake cigarette
box. 500 cigarettes." I mean, that's
probably how many cigarettes you could
buy with the price this [\h__\h] is. Why are
you guys voting yes, chat? We have to
say no to [\h__\h] Oh my god. We have to
start saying no to [\h__\h] We have to
start saying no to [\h__\h] This is stupid.
Fine. Whatever. They voted yes. It's on
the list. Okay, next. See, now this is
cool. Like, this is really cool. This is
a Oh my god, this is actually so cool. I
might just buy this anyway. I don't even
know if this is some content [\h__\h] chat.
Look at that. Handmade flower mushroom
lamp,
like an enchanted forest. See, this is
awesome. But the problem is it's just
like I'm just going to plug it in and
it's going to sit there. But maybe we
could do it at the start of stream and
then it would sit in the it would be the
vibe for the episode. It' sit on the
side of the table. This is AI. What do
you mean it's AI?
Wait, this isn't a real image? Yeah, it
is.
No, it's not.
Is that a real image? That looks real to
me. This looks like [\h__\h] AI.
Is this a real image?
No, it's real.
Whoever's Whoever's filming this has
really [\h__\h] shaky hands. [laughter]
That that their hands are too shaky for
it to not be uh or for it to be AI. I
still don't know if it's worth buying.
It's not I if we buy it, it would just
be in the video. I don't think we buy
that. God, people voted [\h__\h] yes. Oh
my god. Okay, fine. But we're gonna have
to remove [\h__\h] next. See, now this is
awesome. This is the type of [\h__\h] that
I've wanted. Now we're [\h__\h] cooking,
chat. A sunshine steel tongue drum.
I could play some [\h__\h] songs on this
[\h__\h] This is that stuff, dude. I is
This isn't This is the one that they
have like on like resorts where they're
playing like some island music. This is
the one that they have in like water.
And there's this one guy on TikTok that
like fills it with water and plays it
with his fingers and he serenades me at
3:00 a.m. before I go to sleep. I love
that guy's videos. Don't know his name,
but he shows up in my for you page. All
right, 82% yes. Knew that was going to
be a yes. Next slime. Honey slime
straight from the hive. Do not eat. I
think I'm going to disobey that order,
especially if it smells like honey. Bee
honey clay Icy jelly slime DIY slime
stretchy scented.
Not a fan of the [\h__\h] that they put
in it though. Like I'm tossing that in
the trash. Whenever I've played with
slime, I just like a smooth slime, you
know? I don't want to put like weird
like things in it. Ruins the texture for
me. That actually kind of looks like
diarrhea.
That's kind of gross. I thought it would
be more like one one texture
that looks like poop. Oh, no. It's a
hard no. I think I think that picture
where it looked like [\h__\h] made a lot of
people vote no.
All right. Okay. Next one. Lost in the
cheese. There's no way that's what it
says in Japanese above it. Or is that
Korean? There's I feel like that's a lot
of characters for that to say Lost in
the Cheese. Please forgive me. It
probably says wa It's slurs.
No, it's not. Wow, these people actually
kind of look like they're wearing the
Lost in the Cheese shirt. Are they
modeling this?
No way. Buy it for Cohard. Wow, that's
getting a no from chat. Has my chat
grown from the brain rot? Has my chat
defeated the brain? Has my chat evolved?
First they vote no to the 67 fidget
spinner
and then they vote no to the lost in the
cheese shirt. Chad, I think you guys are
evolving. All right. How about goose
mittens?
Another useless [\h__\h] product. It's
like they also would look nothing like a
goose if they weren't making that shape
with their hands. Like if you just put
your hands by your sides, it would just
look like you're wearing like white and
orange mittens. This one's kind of cool.
It's a couple's portrait custom doll.
So, I think I would submit a picture of
me and Brooke and then they would make
like handk knitted dolls or crochets
of me and Brooke and then that would be
I guess kind of cool to see how accurate
it is. Or do I just send in a bunch of
stupid pictures of myself? No, I think I
should do a real one. I think Brooke
would like that. That's like a cute
gift. This is honestly like a cool
Valentine. Yo, for people in chat, I'm
not trying to glaze this seller right
now, but I mean it's only like 16 bucks.
Oh, it says up to 60, so I'm assuming
when you customize it probably changes.
That's a pretty cool gift. A haunted
doll. I feel like this is probably not a
good purchase. A haunted doll. See a
25-year-old spirit murder victim. See,
here's the problem is I'm not keeping
this in my room.
I'm throwing this in the trash after I
get it. I feel like I don't want to buy
that. [laughter] I I don't chat. I don't
believe in ghosts like that. Seriously,
but I don't want to buy a 25 I don't
want to buy a 25-year-old murder victim
doll.
Also, why are we selling this? Oh my
god, there's a video of it.
Oh my god. And the EMF readers [\h__\h]
pinging. Hell no.
Hell no.
Oh, it would come back. All right, I
burn it. CIA is a 25-year-old spirit
with a beautiful French accent. She was
born in Paris. Her mother was a real
respected runway model but was cancelled
after giving birth. Her mom and father
met on one at once at the shows. She
started doing modeling ads at 2 years
old, travel the world. She had the best
tutors. She walked home one evening when
a stranger attacked her, raped her, and
slit her throat. I'm not buying this.
No, I don't even care if I've used my
videos. I'm not buying that. I feel like
that's like [\h__\h] up. Why are we
selling that?
Why are we Who Why are we selling that?
And who's going, I want to buy that.
That's [\h__\h] weird. You're a [\h__\h]
liberal. I'm a [\h__\h] liberal because I
don't want to buy a haunted murdered
doll. No. What? That's not even like the
fear of it. I just feel like that's
weird. The bean. What is this hole? And
it looks wet.
It kind of reminds me of the frog
from Teu.
I wonder who made this. This is like
handmade.
Like there's somebody there's somebody
in the world that handmade this frog
that I bought for like $12. Yo, I swear
to God that looks like a camera.
[laughter] Yo, I'm now trying to tweak
out now that I'm like looking at it.
That looks like a camera in its eye.
The CIA looking at me just stare at the
stare into the camera. Oh no. Do we buy
the bean? People are voting yes for the
bean. All right. Yes for the bean. Next
is uh the yodelling pickle. A plush doll
stocking stuffer desktop office toy
stress relief gag gift. Hilarious
yodelling pickles. My favorite stocking
stocking stuffer.
Delightfully annoying.
Why you need the annoying pickle? Our
favorite customer quote. Who needs a
husband when you could have a yodelling
pickle.
It's hard to not laugh when you hear the
annoying pickle. Students give you a
hard time. Press the pickle and get
their attention instantly. Wow, look at
the family laughing at the yodelling
pickle. Guaranteed to pickle your fancy.
Team bonding, gag gift, stress relief,
conversation starter. That's how you
know they appeal to the [\h__\h]
computers that are roaming the earth
right now. The [\h__\h] the lizard
creatures.
Conversation starter. What? What? I'm
buying it.
Uh, shark survival kit. I've seen these
on Tik Tok shop, so I'm not really
surprised they're selling them on Etsy.
uh has a uh handy dandy disposable
undies, uh booty wipes to clean your
ass, uh brown paper bag to dispose of
your [\h__\h] uh and your [\h__\h] covered
underwear.
Uh what else?
Remove your nasty, shitty underwear. Use
the booty wipes to clean your ass. Put
clean, disposable underwear on your
fresh ass. Place your shitty underwear
and booty wipes in a brown paper bag or
just throw them in the trash. Why do you
have to put them in a bag? Show off your
new keychain to let everyone know you
survived a shard. Damn, dude. This would
be handy to have, but like I think I
would just freeball that [\h__\h] Like if I
sharded in public, I'm just going to
throw my underwear out and then just go
home. I thankfully have never sharded in
public, but I've sharded multiple times
at home.
You shard at home, too. You go
having a conversation, so yeah, I'm just
kind of like
your eyes widen.
It's like you don't know what to do.
Multiple times. Yeah, usually when I had
the stomach virus. When I turned 21, I
sharded myself like multiple times. I
had the stomach virus like twice in a
month. When I turned 21,
you guys voted no for Wait, did we pull
for the shark survival kit or was that
the yodelling pickle? Are we buying the
shark survival kit? You guys don't know
good products. I mean, are you [\h__\h]
kidding me?
No, I'm eating. We're buying the shark
survival kit. There's so many other lame
ass products y'all said yes to. Hold on.
We have two more things. And then we're
gonna have to go through the other ones.
Another one. See, we could cut out the
other one. Man walks into a bar. Over
6,000
of the most hilarious jokes, funniest
insults, and gutbusting oneliners.
This [\h__\h] is something Michael Scott
would use, bro. Oh my god. Look how
thick that is. Like a dictionary. That's
like the Bible of [\h__\h] jokes. I'm
down to get this one and then remove the
insult one cuz they're the same thing.
Arnold and Haskins. Man walks into a
bar. Got to get that. We'll remove the
other one because they're basically like
the same thing, but this one has way
more jokes and way more bang for your
buck. All right. Last thing. I have no
idea what this is.
A Halda Clark 5 feet frequency zapper.
Does it like electrocute you? You hold
copper rods and turn up electronic
frequencies.
It shocks you. Does it hurt?
Shows a picture of a happy old woman.
Is this supposed to be like therapeutic?
What the [\h__\h] do you do with this? I had
the best night's sleep after only one
use. Is it supposed to make you calmer?
Oh, this has like a hundred reviews.
What is What is this?
A Halda Zapper. What is a Halda Zapper?
A Hold Five frequency zapper is a
battery operated electronic device on
the theories of Halda Clark to eliminate
parasites, bacteria, and toxins from the
body. Okay, so it's pseudocience.
So I electrocute myself and that that'll
get rid of the bacteria in my body.
What the [\h__\h] Increase the likelihood
of targeting specific pathogens.
30 kohertz. How strong is that? Like
would I feel the shock? How strong is 30
kilhertz?
Significant and often painful
sensations.
What? And this is supposed to eliminate
bacteria in my body. What is this? What
is this like weird 120p picture of
somebody's like is this somebody's heart
rate? What the [\h__\h] is this? What does
that have to do with anything that
somebody they have the world in their
hands? What does that have? It's going
to eliminate [laughter] pathogens. I
think this thing's going to give me a
heart attack.
Excellent product. Use it several times.
does exactly what it claims to do. It's
removing pathogens from your body.
I don't understand. I I don't understand
when people are like, "I need this."
Well, I don't I I don't I don't get it.
And it's $161 and I'm supposed to listen
to this old woman that tells me it's
good for me.
I'm down to buy it. Does the Hold Does
the Hold Zapper work? Oh, she got sued
by the FTC.
Oh god. It says it's a cure for cancer.
Oh wow. This is like pseudocience
[\h__\h] There's like there's like
articles. The Swiss study group for
complimentary and alternative methods in
cancer
by Halda Clark. I need to buy this now
just to see what the [\h__\h] it even is.
Oh, it's such a waste of money though.
Okay, we got to remove some things. I
think we have 30 products. We got to
remove like a few of them. Rat
taxiderermy. We're keeping Captain
America shield fire. Keeping husky ear
keeping. Danny Deito. Awesome. Blue
brain eye. Pretty cool product.
What's something that's stupid that you
guys said yes to? I'm looking at this.
Okay. Can we move the rock fidget slug?
That's a stupid product. The foot
candle.
I know. I want to know what it smells
like though. Like the foot candle is
kind of intriguing
on a deeper level. Oh, the mushroom
lamp. It's just boring content. It's a
cool product though. Do you guys really
want me to get the retro cigarette box?
This is stupid.
I'm gonna It's $52. I'm going to open
it. I'm going to blow bubbles once and
I'm going to go. This is a waste. Don't
keep it. Okay, we'll get rid of it. I
think I I don't know. I'm down to do
more than 25. I just don't want like to
be buying useless [\h__\h]
H the real Minecraft Bluetooth speaker.
I don't want to say it's useless, but
it's like,
bro, it's just a speaker in a [\h__\h]
wooden box. Can we Can we It's just a
It's a speaker in a wooden box. You get
the discs. You have to pay for the
discs. With the discs, it's $130.
You just get the D. Like I'm just buying
I'm just buying a bad speaker in a
wooden box. We're going to get rid of
that. That and then we'll buy everything
else. That's 26 products. Okay. So, what
we're going to get
is as follows.
Both rat taxiderermies.
A Captain America shield. Husky ears and
a tail. Danny Deito. The weird blue
brain eye. thick Pokemon cards, a hot
dog glass pipe, I'm a fat chud t-shirt,
a magic conchk shell, mail from Bart
Coppins himself, a Carolina Reaper like
spicy thing, a ray gun replica, a a 67
fidget spinner. I think I added that One
Piece press on nails. Uh, the medieval
like cosplay, circumcision survivor
t-shirt, foot candle, tongue drum,
couple doll, the bean, yodelling,
pickle, shark survival kit, a jokebook,
the weird zapper, and gloving. Not the
fidget spinner. Then we would have 25 if
we removed the fidget spinner. All
right, we're taking out the fidget
spinner. Get a butt plug. I'm not I
cannot review a butt plug on stream. All
right, that's what we'll do. I'll order
those. The part two of this stream
slashv video probably gonna be like a
month from now because we gotta wait for
all this to come in and a lot of this
stuff is custom so
it might take
you know I don't know how long but it
might take a minute. So we'll order
those go from there. Sound good?
Awesome. We have an Etsy review.
Dub in the chat. Dub in the chat. So,
um, about a month, it might have been
over a month ago, it might have been
like two months ago. This has probably
been the longest time gap from buying
the products to actually reviewing the
products that we've ever had. Uh, for
the YouTube viewers, it's instantaneous.
But for [laughter]
for us, it has been two months. It is
now Easter day at the time that I'm
reviewing this. I think I bought these
products in like late February. Did I
buy them in March? It's been over a
month. Uh, we've done an Amazon review.
We've done a Teeu review. I think that's
it in terms of like largecale like
buying chats suggested products. But we
did Etsy this time around and there are
a lot of handmade products. So, some of
the things took forever to come in. Uh,
but they're finally in now. Um, before
we even get started, I do have to say,
well, this is kind of getting started.
One of the products came in broken.
Okay. Uh, so do you want to take a guess
what it was for the people that even the
YouTube viewers would be able to guess
because they know the products that I
ordered cuz it's literally they saw it 5
seconds ago. Uh, but for stream, you
might not remember anything that we
bought. I kind of barely remember the
things that we got because I've been
kind of acrewing these objects over the
last two months. So, it's going to be
almost like a Christmas day surprise for
me. No, the mouse did not break.
actually to start off the review.
We have a taxiderermy ma taxiderermy's
mouse holding a monle and I believe some
sort of pipe. His feet are very sharp.
This is a dead rat. This is a dead mouse
for the people. This is taxiderermy.
Uh, it's I would say cute as well as
kind of creepy. Uh, I don't really know
how I feel about taxiderermy.
I don't really know how I feel about
taxiderermy. Uh, if it's like uh an
Okay, I'm going to say this. People that
go hunting and then they put like their
deer head on the wall. I feel like
that's a different level of tax than
this. But um that is disturbing because
I always feel like they're looking at
me. Whereas this is kind of cute and not
it doesn't upset me as much. I hope the
rat lived a wonderful life though cuz
now he's a stuffed animal. Who What are
your thoughts on stuffing pets?
I would say that's a no-go. I would say
if you stuff your pet that's creepy.
Stuffing a pet's weird. Stuffing a rat,
maybe not so much. Uh but there's a lot
there's a small not a lot there's a lot
of people but a small subsect percentage
of pet owners uh that for some reason
when they're like Chihuahua or you know
[\h__\h] golden retriever or whatever
dies they go oh I know I'm going to get
it skinned and stuffed. What the [\h__\h]
Sorry. You know that was a good start.
Now we have to we'll get it out of the
way. Uh I'm very upset about this. I'm
not going to refund it because I don't
really think it's the uh seller's fault.
More so UPS handling the package, but
um this is going to upset some people.
The uh
the ray gun, the ray gun that was uh a
lot came in broken.
So, it came with a mystery box, which I
did not know that it would, which I
think is also a cool addition. So, I'm
not going to knock the seller for this.
Uh, but it did come in broken. This part
was supposed to be stuck on like this,
so it would have looked like a perfect
ray gun and you would have been able to
reload it, too. Um, I think I'm still
going to keep this. I think there's a
world where I just super glue this back
on and it kind of just is fine. I would
super glue it. Adapt has one. Yeah,
they're really cool. Uh it also has like
movable parts. I think Adapts might
actually glow. This is like an Etsy
seller. This is definitely 3D printed,
but it's heavy. Uh and it probably took
a while to make. So, I'm not, you know,
turbo upset about it, but I I did expect
at least one product to come in broken.
So, I'm I you know, I'm It's shitty that
it's that one, but I'm happy it was only
one. Um, but yeah. So,
how this is going to work is we're going
to review each of these products. And
normally I kind of review them and then
we move on and I kind of just go through
each product. I feel like it would be
fun to give it not a rating, but a is it
worth it? You know, because if I'm
buying a product on Amazon or Teeu, it's
not really coming from an individual
seller. Most of the time it's like big
business, whereas this is a lot of like
individual sellers. And I think we
should do would I recommend this
product? That one is going to get
voided. I'm not going to have an opinion
on that because I couldn't review it
because it was broken. I'm not upset at
the seller though. But we have to do the
the taxiderermy mouse. I would give this
a worth it. I think this was like $30.
Uh, which, you know, maybe a lot of
money for a dead rat, but you know,
somebody had to stuff it and also super
glue his butt to this funny chair and
give him a monle. Oh, sorry. And give
him a monle and whatever weird pipe
thing this is. I think it's a pipe. Do
we want an up and close of the dead rat?
I would keep him in the background. Like
I would say it's worth it because I
would put him here.
I don't know. He doesn't really fit
there, does he? I got a lot of Funko
Pops and like Smekis and other [\h__\h]
Give him a name.
What do we name him? Leo. Leo. Le. Is it
a rat or a mouse? That's going to change
what I name it. This is a mouse, right?
Rats are a lot bigger. I saw a rat in
Boston for the first time. I've been in
New York many a time. Been in Philly
many a time. I know they have rat
problems. They're little sneaky devils.
You don't see them a lot. Maybe in the
subway, but you don't really see them.
When I was in Boston, I saw a [\h__\h]
a hog of a rat just run across the
street. I was like, whoa.
Whoa. That thing could eat through
drywall. Remy, that's lame. I like
Eustace. Wait, he needs some sort of uh
professional name. You know, he's a very
he's a very classy guy. He has an
Abraham Lincoln top hat on. Uh and
obviously he's into the fine arts, so
something he needs a first and a last
name. Eugene Blumin.
Okay. See, now we're starting out. I
This was a bit of a grab bag. This is
not We have higher quality products than
this. Trust me. This I We didn't We
weren't just buying taxiderermy rats and
3D printed objects from Etsy. This is
This was entirely chat's idea for me to
get this. This is Danny the Cheeto.
Uh it's actually pretty solid. Uh oh,
and it's a magnet.
Danny Deito will live there. Do you
think he'll melt?
He's kind of staring at the surface of
the sun right now with a lava lamp. Put
it on a YouTube plaque. Hey buddy, those
are made of me. Those are made of Wait,
this will actually be the real or fake
test on YouTube blacks.
They're made of wood if you didn't know
that. If you cut into a YouTube plaque,
they're made of wood. They're just like
I think there's a very thin uh level of
like metal, but they make it like more
shiny. They had to cut a lot of corners
cuz uh there's so many YouTube plaques
that have been getting shipped out. Like
YouTube Shorts made it a lot easier for
channels to get a lot of subs and
YouTube as a platform's a lot bigger. So
the the the plaques have been changing
constantly. Next next actual product. I
actually see one I'm going to grab.
It's a magic conchk from Spongebob. If
you were a Spongebob fan when you were a
kid, this is a magic conchk. And it is
pullable.
I did put batteries in it. I had to make
sure that was the only thing I want to
say. I did not review these products
prior to stream, but a lot of them,
similar to the team reviews, require
batteries or some form of assembly. Um,
so it is the magic conchk. I need to ask
it a question, don't I? Wait, let's make
sure let's make sure it works first.
>> Yes.
>> Okay, that was a little weird. Temporary
gain increase just so you could hear the
conchk. [snorts] Bit of an ASMR.
Magic conchk.
Am I gay?
>> I know you want to, but you can't right
now.
>> Okay, so it's saying I can't be gay
right now, but that's okay. I can be gay
later. Um, it's another question. I
don't really know what else I would ask
it. It looks like a rose toy. It's not a
[\h__\h] rose toy. It's a plastic conch
shell, you dick. Was the moon landing
real?
You may proceed.
>> Okay, that doesn't that doesn't that
doesn't answer the question. Um,
doesn't answer the question. I feel like
we're just getting a bag of tricks here.
We're just we're just pulling out of out
of random I feel like it's it has to be
something that's like answerable. Yes,
no. Maybe she's doing give she's giving
me whole sentences right now. Should I
grow my beard again?
>> Not with that attitude.
>> All right. All right, [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
Just asking you a question.
Jeez, not with that attitude. I don't
even have an attitude.
Being nice.
Wow. Will USA win the World Cup?
>> No.
>> Okay. Wait, this thing's getting a
little more accurate. Wait, this thing's
getting a little more accurate the more
and more we we ask it questions. Okay. I
was just like, a [\h__\h] solid no. I
didn't even I was very curious what the
answer was going to be. Um, would I make
a good fanboy? Go right ahead if you
want to die.
>> Go right ahead if I want to die. What is
this thing giving me? Death threats now.
How many How many uh like voices do you
think is on this?
That's kind of cold, bro. What is
Epstein alive? What am I really gonna
ask a magic conch shell from scene that?
Okay.
>> No.
>> Okay.
I think that's pretty solid.
[snorts]
Another question. Another important
question. It's lying. Were you lying
right there?
>> Do nothing.
>> Okay, that doesn't answer my question.
[snorts]
Uh, are you avoiding Are you avoiding
Are you avoiding what I'm saying right
now?
>> You should go for it.
>> Okay. All right. So, I was starting to
have some level of validity here, but
now I think it's I think it's acting
like it doesn't understand me, but it
does. And so, it's kind of like acting
stupid to make me thrown off from the
whole is Epstein alive thing. Palm Beach
Pete is Palm Beach Jeffrey Epstein.
>> So, what's stopping you?
>> That literally that that has nothing to
do with what I just asked it. It's AI.
Wait. Okay, I'm just going to rapid fire
some answers.
You may proceed. Yes. No. Yes. Without a
doubt,
you no longer have a choice. No. Now is
the optimal time to commit.
Yes.
You could not live with your own
failure. And where did it bring you?
Back to me.
>> I could not live with my own failure.
And it brings me back to you. What in
what word? What question would I have
asked it where that would have been a
valid response?
[laughter]
That was a Thanos line. What the hell?
I feel like they just randomly like AI
put a bunch of Okay, this is a fun
product. Is this worth it? Yes. I think
it was like 40 bucks.
It might have been like $38. editor, can
we throw up the original price of these
products that I paid when I review them
because I'm not going to remember. So,
that'd be really appreciative if you
could have like the price of the product
that I bought. Like, I think this was
like 38 bucks, 35 bucks. I would say
it's worth it. It's a little meme
product. Am I ever really going to use
it much? Probably not. But, you know,
it's not like a throwaway. I'd keep it.
Next we have
something in I didn't get scissors.
[\h__\h] Okay. Wait. I think we'll be able
to open this. Something in in here.
I don't know what's in here, but Oh, I
know what it is. I know what it is.
Does anybody remember what I ordered? I
know what this is.
Ah, [\h__\h] How do I I might have to go
grab scissors real quick. It's a good
product, let me tell you. I haven't even
seen it and I know it's going to be a
good product.
It's getting a thumbs up for me. I
[snorts] was very excited when I ordered
these. Somebody got it right.
Do I say or do I do a big reveal? It's
not cocaine. You think I got cocaine on
Etsy?
I was right. Okay,
for starters,
they come in a wrapping. They come in
their own [\h__\h] foiling package. Like
I'm going to [\h__\h] use that [\h__\h] Card
sleeve.
Do a zoom. We got to get close. Thick
Blastoise.
It's a solid It's a solid gold Pokemon
card. Thick Blastoise. We also have
another one. Another one here. Wait,
what are his moves? Let's zoom in.
Jesus, that was hard. Pause.
Thick Blastoise.
He has moves like soggy bottom
and hydro hands.
Solid metal. Next.
Oh, see this is kind of sad. This feels
like it's
This feels a little [\h__\h] up. Thick
Pikachu.
He has a move called booty clap
and thunder cheeks.
Also solid metal 100 HP. Severe thick
Pikachu can cause a a blinding lightning
storm.
Blastoise. Thick Blastoise leaves you
feeling wet with a single touch. Wow.
My god, these are getting put on
display. And third, I think it's a I
think it's a Charizard.
It might be a Venusaur.
I haven't looked. It's a Charizard. Wow.
See, Fire Ring doesn't even sound like a
[\h__\h] butt related move. Flip a coin
if it fails. Search your deck for thick
Pokemon and put them in your hand.
Discard the other cards.
Blazing Buns. Do you think you could
actually These are like playable cards.
That's what's funny. They're solid
metal, which I love. Dude, this is
[\h__\h] sick. I think this was only like
12 bucks. I mean, they really are just
like printed cards on metal, but this is
awesome. This is like the coolest thing
that I think we pulled. I threw out the
[\h__\h] sleeves. Why would I want a card
sleeve for these? Like, what am I going
to scratch it? It's metal.
Waste of money. It's not a [\h__\h] waste
of money. It's a cool card. What do you
mean? It's not There's no actual MSRP
value on them. There's no MSRP value on
them. They have no resale value because
they're not actually graded Pokemon
cards. They're clearly fakes and you're
not able to keep you're not able to use
them in turning play. It'd be the same
thing as like a duplicate or printed
card. You're not able to use that. So to
me to me that makes it about as about as
worth as a Bulbasaur, but probably from
a bad generation. a little a little
crubbed up, too.
>> Oh, this is like the stupidest [\h__\h]
product. I feel like you I don't
remember I don't remember if this was a
pro. I think I wanted to buy this and
then I it came in and I went, "Why did I
buy this?" The annoying pickle.
It's a yodelling pickle.
How do you [\h__\h] turn him on?
God, I'm staring at his [\h__\h] right
now. Sorry.
You're [crying] late. You're late.
You're late. You're late.
[crying]
>> Does it just infinitely [\h__\h] go? I
pressed the button one time. Oh, he's
died.
Well, that was a long yodel. I feel like
normally you click something, it does
like a little voice line for like half a
second. That was beautiful. I kind of
want to throw him in the trash. I'm not
going to lie. I feel like this is
[\h__\h] landfill material, dude.
Annoying pickle. I think this was like
also 30 bucks. He also has like
shattered legs, dude. You see this?
His limbs are like very flabby.
And I What am I? I think I'm supposed to
lean him on like an edge like this and
he just sits there. This is like some
[\h__\h] you would have at like your
grandparents house, your German
grandmother.
>> Oops.
[\h__\h] Oh my god. He's still yelling.
>> Okay,
I feel like we have we should do a big
product. Should we do a big product now?
No. We have so many small products.
We'll do we'll do like two or three more
small products and we'll do the big one.
A
foot candle.
Why would somebody Oh my god. And this
is See, I was like, what is this? It
doesn't smell like anything. It doesn't
smell like anything. And it's like super
realistic, too. That's what's like
actually the most disturbing about it.
That's like, oh my god, that looks like
a real ass foot.
I don't want to light it because the wax
is just going to drip everywhere. Should
I light it just to get a just to get a
vibe?
No. I feel like I have to light it. All
right. Oh, also peep this sick lighter I
got. It's an oxalottal smoking uh
smoking pipe. Okay. Maybe let's not
light the candle like that.
dude. The wax is already dripping.
The wax is already dripping everywhere.
W [\h__\h] candle. Okay, here's what I'm
going to say. Do I think it's worth the
money I paid for it? No.
Do I think it's a good foot candle?
Yeah. I mean, hyper realistic. Whatever
molding they did on this is fantastic.
Uh, I just don't see a world. It smells
horrid, by the way. I don't know if it's
supposed to smell like foot. It might be
the I feel like I got to let it burn for
a little bit to get the smell. All
right. It's going to leak some wax all
over the place. What do we think the
smell is? I think I selected vanilla.
I'm not getting vanilla.
And it went out. Wait, hold up.
This might be an L product if it can't
stay lit itself.
That's a pretty dimly lit candle, I
might say. The only other problem,
okay, that was definitely me. That was
definitely that was my that was my that
was my breath that that put that out. Uh
I don't like this product. Uh, I don't
think it's worth it, but I still think
it's a good foot candle. I just don't
see a world where I would buy it. But
it's not a bad price for a foot candle.
So, I actually will say good product.
It's in the trash can. I'm never going
to use that. Okay, next. Gloves for
gloving.
Uh, you guys actually didn't want me to
order these. I I if I remember
correctly, and I said, uh, hell no. I'm
def. Okay, that's definitely like an
epilepsy
problem. Okay. Is there any solid color?
Jesus. Is there any solid colors on the
fingertips? Why is it like Christmas
lights? How do I get them to move
normally? Or just like Oh, wait. No, I
could just do only rainbow. There we go.
There we go. There we go. I'm going to
have to turn on I'm going to have to
turn off the lights for this. But Chad,
I've been practicing a routine. Are you
guys ready? I think I do know how to do
one gloving move though and it's going
to look [\h__\h] awesome.
I know there's a whole gloving side of
Tik Tok as well that loves that loves
doing performances and they are pretty
lit. They'll do it to like OG 2012
Monster Cat music. Wow, this looks
actually [\h__\h] awesome. We got to put
on a crazy song. Editor put on a
non-copyright cra like Skrillex X song.
This is the move I know. Wait.
What's like a good gloving move? Hold
up. I got to look up gloving for
beginners.
>> Yo, what is up guys? Puppet here from
glovingacademy.com.
This video features 18 basic gloving
tutorials and is then you're going to do
them all consecutively.
>> Wait,
>> one, two,
>> what? [screaming]
What? How is he doing the finger roll
like that, bro? I can't even get the
glove on. I got some cheap ass gloves,
bro. Dude, I need to invest in higher
quality materials.
Jeez. Okay, wait. Finger hand.
>> One, two, three. Close. Open one hand,
then open the other. Close. Close. Open.
Open. Close. Close. Open. Open. Close.
Close. Now you're going to open each
finger individually. 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4.
Then you're
Yo, it's not that easy. Yo, it's not
It's just not that easy. It's just not
that easy. What the [\h__\h] bro? I feel
like I feel like the the ligaments in my
fingers are not allow Bro, it's just not
that simple. He's finger rolling like so
fast. and combine your wrist together.
With your top hand, you're gonna open
your pointer all the [music] way to your
pinky.
>> N that actually looks fire. Hold up.
They call that move the slingshot. I got
to keep these. Bro, how long do you
think that guy's been gloving for? If
he's that good. I have like the real I
have really shitty gloves now that I'm
thinking about it. How much should I
spend on these? I don't know. I think
it's worth it cuz it's fun, but like
these are these are pretty low quality
gloves.
Like you could you could realistically
get like look at these, bro.
I got the [\h__\h] mittens.
You could probably get better ones for
like way cheaper. I'm very excited for
this.
Man walks into a bar. Over 6,000
of the most hilarious jokes, funniest
insults, and gutbusting oneliners.
Dude, this will carry stream for the
next like six months. My Hawk to a joke.
So all that Hawk to a joke book that I
had from the Amazon review ran out. All
right, let's get one here. Flip to a
random page.
Disabilities.
Oh, wow. They got categories that they
make jokes about here. I don't know.
Dyslexia.
Oh god.
Education college. What's the difference
between a university and an asylum?
This is where you say what? To get out
of an asylum, you have to show some
improvement.
>> [clears throat]
>> How can you tell if an elephant is
sitting behind you in a bathtub?
How
you can smell the peanuts on his breath?
How How do you know there's an elephant
under your bed
when your nose starts to touch the
ceiling?
Why are there a hundred elephant
[laughter] jokes, dude? No, there's no
way. What's the red stuff between an
elephant's toes? Slow pygmies. What does
that even [\h__\h] mean? How does an
elephant hide in a cherry tree? He
climbs to the top and paints his nuts
red.
Wait, that's actually funny. Wait,
that's a good one. That's a good one.
Wait, that's actually a good one. Oh my
god.
What's the difference between an
elephant and a flea? An elephant can
have fleas, but a flea can't have
elephant.
Oh, wow. They have ethnic jokes.
That's great.
Wow. Okay. Ethnic Caribbean. There's two
jokes. When you flip over to Jewish,
there's one, two, three, four pages.
So,
Native American, Scottish, Polish. Yeah,
I don't think I I don't know if I want
to read any of these. Um, dude, the
German the ethnic German joke is a
German joke is no laughing matter. Mark
Twain.
Oh, that's [\h__\h] up. Wait, dude.
[laughter]
These are Who's the author? Stephen
Arnot and Mike Haskins.
My god, dude. I read some of these. Read
them.
Oh god.
Read some of the ethnic jokes. I don't
know if I want to read some of the
ethnic jokes. I feel like we have a we
have 6,000 jokes. Give us one.
A Jewish woman had two chickens. One got
sick, so the woman made chicken soup out
of the other one. That doesn't even make
sense. This is a Russian joke.
A Polish soul soldier is asked who he'd
shoot first if he came across a Russian
soldier and a German soldier. The
Russian soldier replied the poll,
"Business before pleasure. What's 50
feet long and lives on potatoes?" Oh,
this is a different joke. I thought this
was a continuation of the first joke.
What's 50 feet long and lives on
potatoes?
Russians.
What? A Russian meat line. Oh, they have
a whole page of fat yo mama jokes. Yo
mama so fat her dress maker takes her
measurements in light years. Yo mama so
fat I ran around her twice and got lost.
Yo mama's so fat no one can talk behind
her back.
Yo, Mama's so fat she can't even jump to
a conclusion.
Wow, this is multiple pages. Wow, these
are This is six pages of Yo Mama jokes.
[clears throat]
[snorts]
Oh, really? See, imagine somebody just
dissed me. Oh, really?
Your mama's so fat her photograph weighs
10 lbs. Yo, your mama's so fat she was
baptized at SeaWorld. How about now? Oh
[\h__\h] Oh, okay. Your mom was so fat when
she was diagnosed with a flesheating
virus, the doctors gave her 30 years to
live.
What that?
Your mama was so fat when she was
diagnosed with a flesheating virus, the
doctors gave her 30 Oh, cuz she has so
much flesh. Okay. Your mama's so fat she
sells shade in the summer.
Your mama's so fat her belly button
doesn't have lint, it has sweaters.
Dude, this is awesome.
Look how many, bro. Gambling jokes. A
man goes into a butcher shop. The
butcher points to some beef hanging from
the rack and says, "I bet you $10 that
you can't touch that meat." No thank
replies the man. The stakes are too
high.
[\h__\h] stupid. That was like a grandpa
joke.
I made so many bet I made so much money
betting on the Democrats to win the
election that I was able to become a
Republican. Oh god.
Genies and wishes, golf jokes,
hairdressers, health and doctors,
hotels, history.
Dude, this is literally a 500page bug.
How many actors does it take to change a
light bulb?
Sorry, I didn't I just said that word.
Very weird. How many actors does it take
to change a light bulb?
Only one. They don't like to share the
spotlight. Okay. Yeah, I mispronounced
the word bulb. And we're moving to the
next joke. And we're moving to the next
joke. Bro, now it's all just like all
about luck, lying. Dude, some of these
are so long. Oh, this is about marriage
and adultery.
One night, little Johnny's father
overheard his son saying his prayers.
[clears throat] God bless mommy, daddy,
and granny. Goodbye, Grandpa.
>> The next day, grandfather dies. A month
or so later, his father again hears
little Johnny at a prayer. God bless
mommy and daddy and goodbye granny. The
next day, grandmother dies. Father
begins to worry. Two weeks later, he
hears little Johnny praying again.
[clears throat] God bless mommy,
goodbye, daddy. Father nearly has a
heart attack and spends all the next day
in fear of his life. However, he manages
to survive and returns home after work.
I had a really bad day today, he says to
his wife. Don't tell me about bad days,
replies his wife. This morning, the
mailman dropped dead on the porch
cuz the mailman the mailman's the kid's
father.
That's good. That's good one. That's
good material.
Sex jokes. Husband to wife.
[clears throat]
After I shave in the morning, I feel 10
years younger. Uh wife said, "So why not
try shaving before you go to bed?"
What? Because his like dick doesn't work
or something. I'm not a guy.
Tom, Harry, and their wives decide to
spice up their sex life by swapping
partners. Swinging. Later that night,
Tom rolls over in bed and says, "Hey,
Harry, what do you suppose [laughter]
our wives are up to?"
Oh, yeah. That's an instant classic. My
god. Wait. Ah, that one caught me off
guard.
Mice, mistakes, money, insurance, banks,
lottery, poverty, thrift, movies, mommy,
mommy,
neighbors,
optitians, and eyesight. What's the
first joke in the book? Wow, they have a
actual glossery of what jokes you're
looking for. This seems like something
Michael Scott would own from the office.
accents. [clears throat]
The first joke in the book, wait,
actually the first joke in the book
says, "I thought today I'd start by
singing one of the Irving Berlin songs,
but then I thought, why should I? He
never sings any of mine."
First actual joke of the book and then
we're going to move on.
>> A bus stops and two Italian men get on.
They sit down and engage in animated
conversation. The lady sitting behind
them hears one of them say, "Emma, come
first. Then I come." Two asses, they
come together. I come again.
Two asses, they come together again. I
come again and pee twice. Then I come
once more. Oh, should I say this in an
Italian accent?
Emma, I come first, then I come second.
Two asses, they come together. I don't
know how to do it. An Italian accent.
Uh, then I come once more. You
foulmouthed swine, said the lady
indignantly. In this country, we don't
talk about our sex lives in public.
He says, [clears throat] hey, it's all
right.
Replies the man. I'mma just tell my
friend how to spell a Mississippi.
>> [laughter]
>> cuz he was just spelling the word
Mississippi with an Italian accent.
Yeah, we'll read from that book once in
a while. Anyways, next Oh, that ju that
joke book was worth it.
[snorts] AH. [screaming]
OH MY GOD. DID anybody hear the scraping
the scraping plastic noise? Holy [\h__\h]
Oh my god. Anyways,
so kawaii.
There we go. That's a screen grab.
Anyways, uh I don't remember how much
these cost.
probably a bit. I think they're too low.
Like that's better.
They're very high quality, I must say.
Very furry as well.
Somebody please draw this. Why would
somebody draw this? Give it to Koshard.
Should I give these to Koshard? He would
wear them on stream. I actually will
give the I will give these to Koshard.
Chris will wear those. I'm not gonna
wear those. I don't really, you know,
I'm not What am I gonna do with those?
I'm not wearing I'm not wearing the cat
ears often. All right, we'll do one big
product now.
We'll do both big products now. Is that
fair, you guys? And then wait, we still
have a lot more, but I want to get rid
of the items that are large physically.
This is the magic of This is the magic
of production, chat. You're about to
witness it firsthand right here. Watch.
Pivot.
turning.
Boom. I have this medieval like
costume.
I would love to go to a Renaissance
fair. So, this is actually a pretty sick
item.
Am I wearing it right?
I think it looks badass. It's like fit
very well, too. Very hot and sweaty
because it's very thick. But
secondly, and more importantly,
the item everybody's been waiting for.
It's rock [\h__\h] solid.
>> Look at this. It looks like
>> It looks like the top of a trash can,
but it's badass.
Oh my god. Swing it.
Knock somebody in the head, bro. Wait.
Also, it came greasy as [\h__\h] The top of
it so oily.
I don't know what it is. I think it's
like Yeah, I think I don't know if it's
so it doesn't rust or what, but it's
like Yeah, it's like a polish, but it
gets all over my clothes.
How much do we think it cost?
>> It weighs like 30 lb. This was $350.
This is the most expensive thing we
bought
for this
as much. Actually, how much was the uh
Iron Man helmet for the Amazon review? I
think that might have been 400, but
around the same price. Big ass item.
Sick as [\h__\h]
Could literally just sit in a corner
and I love it. Diverting back to regular
setup.
Hold up. Hang it on the wall. It weighs
way too much.
I It weighs way too much. I could hang
it on on a wall in a different room, but
there's also nowhere to put it. My
background's like full. Where would I
put that, chat? If I were to hang it on
the wall, I think it's worth it. You
know, I think it's a very expensive
product, but um you know, if you were
like cosplaying as [\h__\h] Captain
America or some [\h__\h] that's like a real
shield. Ooh, under the table.
No, cuz it's going to have a reflective
glare. The That's the problem, too, is
it's a shiny metal. It's just going to
be It's going to be even worse than the
plaques. I'll think about it, but I It's
probably not going to work under the
table because it'll just reflect.
But I I think I should go as Captain
America this Halloween. At least at some
point for one outfit, I got to go as
Cap. And I got to get a real suit, too.
Not some [\h__\h] from Spirit Halloween. You
know how badass that would look if I had
a real Captain America suit? Like
[\h__\h] some uh like Winter Soldier
likeesque [\h__\h] movie. Oh my god.
Like this, bro. This would be actually
straight Aura
if I had like a skin tight real [\h__\h]
cosplay fit with a big ass shield. I
actually think the shield might be a
little too big. We got the biggest size
and I told Chad I wanted to get one
smaller and I think I would have been
right cuz I think my shield's actually
bigger than his shield.
My shield's huge. Either way, sick
product. I'm not upset about it.
Was it worth would I would I regularly
spend $350 on it? No. But I do think if
you were a cosplayer, it's worth or just
a super Captain America fan. We still
have a shitload of more products. But
that was the um
that was the big items that we had to go
over. We actually will change into one
of the shirts. We have two shirts here.
We could wear we could wear one for one
section, one for the other. First one.
I'm such a fat [\h__\h] chud. And second
one,
circumcision survivor. Now
we Which one should we wear first?
We could wear one for like three opens
and then another one for three.
Everybody's saying two first. We'll wear
the chud one second. Sorry, nipples are
out. Sorry, nipples are out.
All right.
Circumcision survivor
would never wear this out. I would wear
the I'm such a fat [\h__\h] chud in
public. I don't think I would stroll
into like a restaurant wearing a
circumcision survivor shirt. It actually
depends on the restaurant. I think if it
was like a uh Applebee's,
you know, the the bar is real low on
entry. like an Applebee's or a Chili's
or something. Yeah, I' I'd probably
stroll in wearing this [\h__\h] but the the
Chud shirt would be reserved for more
fancy occasions like a Buffalo Wild
Wings. Uh or maybe a Texas Roadhouse.
Texas Road House. All right, next
product.
Bro, I forgot about this [\h__\h]
I'm only doing a little.
It's reaper [\h__\h] It's ground reaper
chili. And then they gave me free arable
chili and free Thai pepper. I ordered
one. Okay, number one, I already have to
say this product's worth it because I
bought one vial of this chili and they
gave me two packs of dried peppers for
free.
This is what we bought.
It's reaper. It's reaper seasoning.
I'm going to smell it.
Yeah.
Immediately I feel like sweat building
on my forehead. It's like every review
I'm putting my foot down. Okay. I'm
saying after this [\h__\h] review, any
future, like if we go back to Amazon or
we do Tik Tok shop or some [\h__\h] I'm not
doing something that's absurdly spicy.
I'm putting my foot down. And I know we
have the food gauntlet after this where
I have to buy like gross foods and [\h__\h]
but like bro, I'm not I I'm It's like
every sing Bro, that's not Boo chat, you
guys. It's not fun.
I'm not Okay. Yo, thank you for the
[\h__\h] free Thai pepper and free arble
chili. I'm not eating these. I'm not
eating these. I'm going to put a little
Maybe I'll eat one.
Let's see. I'll Okay, maybe I'll eat
one. Let Maybe I'll eat one. I Okay, you
guys. Okay, I'll eat one. But God, see,
I caved to peer pressure instantly. I c
like I didn't even I I caved to peer
pressure in Okay, I just need to see how
this goes. I need to see how this goes.
I'm gonna put a little bit on a napkin.
God damn it. I'm also see I I don't
think this is going to be too bad
because I've had I've had the one chip
challenge twice. I've had some hot
[\h__\h] ramen and I did the Dave's Hot
Chicken challenge.
Uh which I believe is Reaper. So is this
Yeah, this is Reaper because Ghost
Pepper is less than Reaper. Reaper is
more spicy. This is 100% organic
Carolina Reaper powder. So this is just
ground up Carolina Reaper.
I'm going to lick my finger.
I'm going to put it in the sauce and
then I'm going to touch my tongue with
it and lick it off. Pause. Okay, I will
show you the powder as well. But
[snorts] I'm not [\h__\h] doing I'm not
eating this [\h__\h] like it's a [\h__\h]
pixie stick. Okay, if you came into this
goddamn stream or review thinking that
I'd [\h__\h] down the whole vial, you're
crazy. I'm not snorting it. You I would
have to go to the hospital if I had to
snort this. That calls like respiratory
failure.
I should use like a pinky. Wash your
hands.
Wash your hands. Wash your hands.
Oh, it's just like hot Cheeto dust.
>> [cough]
[cough and clears throat]
>> is See, it's every time, bro.
It's every time I get mad confident.
[clears throat]
Every time. See, I got to stop coughing
that all over the place.
Every time I get so confident,
I go, "Oh, it's not that bad."
And then it just builds.
It just builds every time.
It's not as bad as the one chip because
I only that amount of power powder.
[snorts] Oh god, I got to spit.
It makes your mucus it makes your mucus
like real thick. I'm not exaggerating,
you [\h__\h] dick. [snorts]
It makes your mucus you real thick.
And it's it it like starts out not that
bad. Kind of like a habanero. And I eat
habanero all the time.
But then it just builds on the tip of
your tongue and it feels like somebody's
stabbing you. But it's not as bad as the
one chip because I only had like, you
know,
an eighth or a tenth of like the one
chip's powder. Not even. But it's still
ass.
It's definitely still ass. I actually
don't think there's any amount of money
for me to do the entire vial.
Like I put my I put my [\h__\h]
my my pinky finger on it and it's still
burning on the tip of my tongue.
Like that shit's hot. It's subsiding a
little bit quicker, but um yeah, 13
billion. Oh yeah, a billion dollars. But
I'm saying there's no realistic amount
of money.
A billion dollars though. Yeah. All
right, I'll try one of these chilies.
Can we look up the Scoville level on
these? Thai pepper
arble chili. If I had to guess looking
at them, the Thai pepper looks spicier.
Usually the ones that crinkle more and
get like really [\h__\h]
indented
are the spicier ones. 50 to 100k for
Thai pepper. I feel like I can handle
that though.
How much is a habanero? Cuz I eat h I'll
eat a habanero. Oh, a habanero could be
up to a 200k. Yeah, I'll eat one of
these.
I'll eat one of these. I'm eating a tiny
one, though. But I I'm pretty sure the
more crinkled they are.
Oh, yeah.
The more crinkled they are, the spicier
they tend to be because there's more
like room for the pith
because most of the spice
It's still spicy. [laughter]
It's like swelling my tongue a little
bit. Some of the pith or like the spine
or whatever is what makes it hot.
[snorts]
All right, I'm eating this.
Bro, you know what I should have done?
Whenever I do these [\h__\h] challenges
like bro v bro, I know I can handle
this. Not in the sense of like I'm going
to enjoy it, but like I'll I'll get
through it. I've done the one chip
twice. I I know what the Carolina Reaper
pain is like. And every time I do these
broy bros, it's like, "Oh, cover
yourself in mayo. Dance to crazy frog,
[\h__\h] Let's bet a one chip.
Let's bet a you have to eat five
havanero peppers in a row because what
the [\h__\h] Imagine if Jinxy lost and
instead of doing the banana challenge,
banana sprite, he had to eat like a
ghost pepper. That would be so much
funnier.
It would be way worse for the person and
the stakes would be so high. I'm
sweating.
All right, [\h__\h] it. One bite. Everybody
knows the rules.
It took it right back out. Took it right
back out. Took it right back out. So,
as I was going to bite down, it was
really hard and I caved. I have to eat
it. I have to eat it. I have to eat it.
Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Wow.
It's like in my teeth. I see like I I I
It's not that bad right now, but I I
don't like guessing cuz it'll just hit
you randomly.
I'm not I'm not kid I don't have milk. I
don't own milk.
But I don't like going, "Oh, that wasn't
that bad." Because then sometimes it'll
just sneak up on you. It's hot. It's
like a habanero. It's like a habanero.
Habanero hot. Like I think people don't
understand. Like a lot of people in my
chat
that like it's hot as [\h__\h] Like I'm
trying to talk through it. A lot of
people in my chat will be like, "Oh,
you're just a [\h__\h]
You can't do the [\h__\h] Carolina
Reaper." But like
what's the hottest thing you guys have
eaten? Some of you have probably had one
chip. Some of you have probably had a
ghost pepper Carolina Reaper. But for
the most part, the spiciest thing an
average person has had is like a spicy
hot sauce at like a Buffalo Wild Wings.
That is
literally It's getting It's getting
hotter. That is literally nothing
in comparison to like a Carolina Reaper.
Like you having a blaz one blazing
boneless wing at Buffalo Wild Wings. Get
the [\h__\h] out of here. And it builds.
That's the thing that's scary about it.
It smells like death
and it builds. This is just like a hot
ass habanero pepper.
That's all it really tastes like. Like
on my eggs in the morning, I put
habanero Tabasco.
It tastes good. Oh my god, I'm actually
sweating.
And I know people are saying I'm faking
it. Literally look at my forehead.
It's hot. It's hot. Like I'm not
exaggerating that it's hot. I can't
force myself to sweat. Yeah. I'm
throwing this [\h__\h] out. I'm throwing
this [\h__\h] out. I'm not eating those. I
got to go wash my hands real quick. I
got to go wash my hands real quick. L
waste. Oh. Oh. L Waste. Yeah. Let me go
donate the Carolina Reaper powder to a
soup kitchen, you stupid [\h__\h] They're
really going to use that in their
dishes. Oh. Oh, hey homeless guy.
Instead of giving you food or something,
here's Thai chili peppers. Have fun
eating that. [\h__\h] four calories.
You're going to burn more by sweating.
Next. This is actually a really cool
product. I'm not going to be able to
wear them, but it is a very cool product
and I think they're a fan.
We bought press on one piece nails.
Those are tough. And you know how I knew
they knew me? You know how I know
they're a fan? Chat,
hold up. My dumb ass can't get this. The
little pokey thing stabbing through.
They like crocheted.
Look at this.
A possum. Is this crochet or knitting?
I don't know. But look at that.
That's probably so hard to do. They gave
me a letter, too. I'm still sweating.
Sorry. I'm going to read it on stream.
Sorry, it's so hot. They gave me frog
stickers, too.
Hi, Joe. Thank you so much for
purchasing uh from me. It means a lot.
My boyfriend Anthony showed me your
videos and I've enjoyed them since. I
also wanted to include a little possum
puppet with your order. My friend Ishri
Ishri, I think I'm saying it right. I sh
H R E. Holy [\h__\h] Ishri made it.
However, once we found out you bought a
nail set, we wanted you to have it. Hope
he's in good hands. Thank you again. I
hope the nails fit well. If you can
leave a review, it helps a lot. Always
enjoy the content. W [\h__\h] Etsy owner,
Etsy business owner, editor, throw up
their store at if you want good press on
nails. You know where to find them. I
don't have nail glue. So that's why I
will I'll put I'll show them, but I
don't have nail glue. Ask Brooke to wear
them. Brooke has nails currently. I
think I'm gonna keep I'm going to put
them back in this and I'm going to give
them to Brooke and see if if they fit
her. But they're for my fingers. Like,
they're based off of my fingers.
Be very careful here, chat. Be very
careful. I think this one's Luffy. Look
at that.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Well, I can't
I need nail glue, but it fits perfectly.
Yeah. It's old Straw Hat Luffy.
This is sick.
Should I try to see if they fit Brooke?
I'll do that later. And if they do fit
Brooke, because I don't know if Brooke's
fingernails are like mine. Sorry, I'm
still dealing with the heat. If they fit
Brook's nails, I'll add a clip on the
YouTube video of her putting them on.
But these are fire. I'm going to keep
these. And where should I put the little
possum guy?
I feel like I need to keep this, too.
Wrap this around like this. That's
[\h__\h] sick as well.
W Etsy business lock in chat. We have
>> We have like 10 more things. Nine more
things. This one's actually [\h__\h]
awesome. Also, that product's worth it.
W product. I was already shouting it
out, so I assume that was known.
It's really weird. It's a realistic eye
in like a a squishy like Papa Meesque
brain.
And it comes with eye eye gloop. Eye
lubricant.
Should I put eye lube on him? I think
that it kind of has eye lube on him
right now. I think it's if you can't
move him around,
you need to put eye lube. I think this
thing was like $60.
But isn't it kind of sick though? Should
I have it look at chat in the
background? Dude, we have way too many
things on this on this [\h__\h] Hold up.
I'm making an executive decision. That
alien chill beer guy is is getting
shelved from the background because he
needs to sit on a ledge. He's gone.
Okay.
And he's getting replaced
by brain by brain eye.
Oh, and uh and Eugene Blumin. Oh god, I
think I just like protruded his stomach.
Two new additions to the background of
stream. Eugene Blumin,
[\h__\h] you. Put him on the lava lamp.
That's unsafe, chat. He's a plastic
product. Then that thing gets hot.
And Eugene Blumin. You know what?
Oh god, he's out of frame. He's out of
frame. Put him on the fridge.
I'll put him on the fridge, but you guys
won't be able to see him. That'll be the
jump scare of a lifetime if he ever
falls.
Oh, in the fridge,
Chad. He doesn't sit up. Doesn't sit up.
He His His body design is not made for
anything but sitting on like a ledge.
Wait.
Bang. Post it on the Twitch heart. Oh,
we didn't name him.
We didn't name him. What do we name our
little I don't need the eye lube.
What do we name him? Can I pop his eye
out of his head?
Sorry, I had to smell it. I can flip him
around. It's a very realistic eyeball as
well. Look at that.
It's [\h__\h] creepy. Ivore.
Ivore the eye. I kind of like that.
And he'll look up at chat. Ivore the
eye. Next. I think this is our last
little like fidget thing.
Bean. That product's worth it, by the
way. Don't care if it's 50 bucks. It's
sick.
Bean.
bean. Wait, they also gave me a free
product. I didn't order this.
They sent me candy.
I don't know if I trust eating that.
They sent me candy. A Chucky sticker,
which is actually sick.
Oh, it's not a sticker.
Is it a sticker?
I can't tell. It's got sticker T. Oh,
wait. I bought bean and they also gave
me.
They also gave me worm.
Now we have Bean and Worm. Bean looks
like he got hit by a car.
He's on his last life.
Does he breathe out of the hole
or pee out of it
or
out of it? I kind of want to eat one of
these candies. Is that unsafe to eat
candy from a miscellaneous Etsy seller?
They sent me Malum Stripes candy
and and Chomp.
And they also gave me a scream sticker
as well. This is kind of awesome. Scream
Chucky Bean.
Bro, they burnt the [\h__\h] Joe into the
worm.
What?
What? And now we have like a whole trio
of like weird creatures.
Now we have a whole trio of like weird
creatures that look at chat.
Bean doesn't really stand up on his own.
That'll be sad. But Bean will Bean will
lay there by himself. Bean and Worm. I
love that. I have no idea how much they
were. I think it was probably like 20 or
30 bucks, but that's still [\h__\h]
awesome. And I only ordered Bean. And
then I also got worm. I mean, it's like
a two for one.
Do we try one of these miscellaneous
candies this guy sent me? Is that
unsafe? Are these They have no nutrition
facts. He just sent me He just sent me
Mauim candy and Chomp. I think I've
actually had Cadbury Chomp. I'll try a
Mau stripes. Is this like Spanish candy?
Oh, they're like pure white. I was
expecting it to be like neon green.
It's UK.
I can have a little bit of gelatin.
chat. Thank you for being concerned
though. I'm not too allergic to a little
gelatin. This is fire.
I just start tripping [laughter]
like like an hour from now. I'm like
when we're done the Etsy review or
watching the the Minecraft video, I'm
like, "Wait."
Oh, it's just so good.
And they're so gummy. Ah, no. We'll save
that one.
We'll save that one. We'll save that
one. That one's very excit Oh.
Oh, yeah. Okay. Yeah. This is why I
brought the grinder down earlier.
So,
this is a hot dog bowl
for tobacco use only. For tobacco use
only, chat. It's a hot dog bowl. Uh, I
don't know if I should clean it. Should
I like rinse it off real quick before I
smoke out of this? We got to put on the
chud shirt. You're right. I haven't put
on the chud shirt. I think I already
have pit stains. Oh, no I don't. But you
can see my nipples
like I'm like I'm on the red carpet
being a little scandalous
for [snorts] free.
Okay, so that's definitely an arm
sleeve. Definitely an arm sleeve there.
Wrong wrong hole. All right. So, editor,
we're gonna have to blur this whole bit
here. But chat, just know that uh we're
going to be using the or for the YouTube
viewers, we're going to be using the hot
dog pipe right now. Uh we'll let you
know how how it goes. Okay. So,
immediate problem with the hot dog
immediate problem with the hot dog bowl
that I'm noticing. It's a very tiny
bowl. Number problem number one. Number
two, the hot dog bun slots are picking
up a lot of the uh fall away. I'm also
going to go out on a limb and say this
is going to scorch my [\h__\h] throat.
This is going to be the worst [\h__\h]
experience. I think we're going to have
a similar experience when we do the 420
review
because during the 420 review, I bought
multiple mystery boxes and it comes with
a lot of different glassear and I think
it's going to be like very obscure
glassware that's like
[\h__\h] shitty. This feels wrong.
This feels wrong. It's very inefficient.
I don't know which way. I don't know
which is I think I'm assuming the skinny
end of the [\h__\h] hot dogs for my mouth
and the thick ends for my finger. Pause.
But Jesus.
All right. So, the takeaway right now
is, does it work? Yes. Is it about as
useful as uh a a cord out apple? Yeah.
Yeah. This is about Joe's hot boxing.
You know how hard it would be to hot box
this room? We'll do it on 420. Probably
not. [snorts]
We'd get my PC fan surprisingly clean.
Surprisingly clean. Like I normally I
like a normal bowl is pretty rough. And
I would say yeah, this is more rough
than like a joint, but
[snorts] it's not bad. It's definitely
not bad. uh annoying to hit because the
bun blocks me from getting closer to the
bowl. So, if I'm using a regular like a
stick lighter, it'd be no problem. But
this lighter, I'm like trying to avoid
burning my [\h__\h] thumb. Do I think
it's worth it? No. Uh this is a funny
product, but not something that I would
actually want to use. Uh there's like
expensive bowls. I would say this is
more of a funny art piece than Okay,
actually it is worth it. Here's why.
Because if you buy it for the purpose of
it being a glass art piece that's like
haha funny hot dog worth it. And then on
top of that, you can smoke weed out of
it. Tobacco use only. Um
but if you're buying it as a bowl, it's
shitty, right? Like this is it. This is
a bad bowl because it's like, you know,
there you just want to have something
that's designed to make it easier to
smoke the weed. Six and a half. I know I
didn't rate any of the other products,
but I I feel like you need you need a
rating on this. The Bull's probably six
and a half. I would say if if this was
like I don't really remember the price.
Editor probably has that up on the
screen. If this was under 20 bucks, I
would say even if it is $20, I would say
it's worth it. If it's anything over
that amount, probably not. We're gonna
hit it one more time. Now we're juiced
up for the rest of the [\h__\h] REVIEW.
LET'S [\h__\h] GO.
Next product is, you guessed it, a card
from Bart. This was $5.
$5. He is a handwritten message and an
individually taken photograph from Bart
himself of a butterfly.
Great photography, Bart. Let's read his
card. [snorts] Dear Joseph, I hope this
card finds you well. In fact, I make
them myself using my own photos. The
species on this photo is one I
photographed myself in Uganda. The
species is
opendra opus. Brilliant nymph is what it
means. I'm doing well in the in the
Netherlands. Spring is about to begin.
That means a new season of breeding
moths is right around the corner. I hope
to do a good video about the buff tip
moth
safal buff buffalis
at least.
Thank you for your interest
uh in my Etsy shop. Uh and it says my I
think it says my shop helps to sustain
my work. Bart Coppins signed.
This is like mad wholesome, right? Like
I feel like this is kind This feels like
the same as like a Patreon. I just sent
him like I sent him like six bucks in
shipping and he [\h__\h] printed out a
photograph of a butterfly he sent
himself or made or took himself on like
dude like what a good photo.
Andy sends me a handwritten [\h__\h]
letter, you know, detailing how his how
his adventures of life are going. And I
don't even know this guy, but Bart
CPins, I wish the best to you, buddy.
Goat. Goat. Should I keep it? Should I
keep the Bart CPins letter? And he wrote
in all he wrote very weirdly.
Like every start of every sentence is
not capitalized, but then he capitalize
he capitalizes every Oh my god. He
capitalizes every letter of every first
of every word. kind of like a YouTube
thumbnail other than is and of.
Put it in the back. I can't keep putting
[\h__\h] in the back, chat. There's too much
stuff in the back. Put it in the drawer.
I have a lot of drawers on my desk.
My [\h__\h] shitty IKEA chat. I built my
gaming desk. Side note, and I asked
Brady about this the other day because I
always have to like fix some of those
the the little pegs on the on the
drawers that hold it up. I have like a
500B
[\h__\h] wooden slab as my desk that's
held up by two metal pegs that I screwed
into the back and two [\h__\h] $60 IKEA
drawers and they make creaking noises
when I like punch the desk and I'm like,
"Dude, is that going to break?" Like, is
that gonna break, man? Next.
Oh god. Wait, sorry. Two products in
one. This is going to be its own thing.
But we do have one more taxiderermy
animal. Uh, this one is only the head of
a mouse.
This one is very disturbing. The other
one. Okay. This one
cute, fancy, risque. Right.
Eugene Blumpkin. This one.
Creepy.
It's a [\h__\h] mouse holding a bottle of
Corona. And guess what?
I thought it was a magnet.
It's not a magnet.
Why would they not put a magnet on it?
Wait, no, that was an option, but they
were sold out of magnets. I remember.
Oh god, the ears move.
Like I'm touching a dead animal right
now. This is
H. I don't know. I don't really like
this one. And they made it smile.
I don't know. I feel like, dude, the
other the other like Eugene Blumin's
badass. This one's kind of creepy,
right?
I mean, it's still like kind of cool.
Where's the second half of his body?
Where's the rest of him? Did we just cut
him in half and then start the and then
we put him on a stand?
Was he mangled to death? Like, see, I
start thinking about how this mouse
died. This is it. I mean, it's just the
skin of the mouse, right? That's really
all it is. Because the hair is fake.
They have to put that in. Or not the
hair, the [\h__\h] whiskers. And then the
eyeballs are fake.
They killed him for your order. I don't
think they killed him for my order. You
think they killed him for my order?
I don't think they did that.
I think they probably just have a slew
of dead rats at the ready.
Rats die very quickly and reproduce like
rabbits.
So, I'm assuming they just have like a
hundred rat felts and then they get an
order and they make it. He really is
cheesing though.
Stop. Oh, I [\h__\h] hate it. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Like, sorry, I was like
looking at his mouth and I was like gh.
All right, next.
This is one of those sick ass What are
they called, chat? Is it a water drum?
Do I need water in it?
No, we do not.
No, we do not. Tell me. Oh my god,
there's a music book. I don't know how
to read music. I thought it was just
going to tell me one through one through
seven. It's telling me notes.
It's a rain drum.
Yeah, but I could play it.
Ready?
[music]
Wait, wait, wait, wait, [laughter] wait,
wait, wait, [music]
wait.
Dude, that sounds like the Minecraft.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
[music]
wait, wait. How do I do it? How do I do
it? How do I do it? How do I do it? No,
that actually sounds like it, right? I
feel like I was hitting that. Everybody
shut the [\h__\h] up. I used to watch these
guys when I was a kid.
It sounds exact. Oh my god. It sounds
like Gravity Falls, too. No, that's
actually awesome. Is this a rain? Like,
are you supposed to put this outside
normally?
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wait, I got it.
Put it in water.
It's meant to be played it not on water.
Is there any way that I I could play
like an easy song? I would love to be
able to play a song.
You're supposed to like drip water onto
it. Okay, hold up. I know what we need
to do.
Did you hear it? Stop saying ew. You
guys asked for this.
What? What are we What are we do? What
do you mean? Ew. What do you mean? Ew.
It's my [\h__\h] raindrum ass. If I want
to spit on it, I'm going to spit on it.
[\h__\h] We asked you to pour water on it.
Yeah, I know. And what do you want me to
go grab a bowl and [\h__\h] submerge this
in water and then get like a [\h__\h] a
syringe and dribble water on top of it,
brother. I mean, that's going to take
like 10 minutes. Let me cook.
[music]
MC finest intro.
[\h__\h] HOLD UP.
I LOST IT. WHAT WAS IT? IT WAS TWO
SOMETHING. It was 24
[music]
supposed to be played on water. Bro, are
we dead ass? Should I actually go grab a
[\h__\h] bowl right now? If I go grab a
bowl and I pour water on this [\h__\h]
thing and it does nothing, I'm going to
be pissed. I'm not doing that. I'm not
doing that. I'm not doing that, bro.
Because you so you heard it already.
It's going to be the same [\h__\h] It's
just going to be a more dull sound. It's
going to be more dull sound. And I can't
read this music.
So, it's cooked.
Oh my god. Wait. No, it says it. No, it
says it. No, it says it. It has the
numbers.
We're doing We're playing a song. We're
playing a song. We're playing a song.
We're playing a song. We're playing a
song. We're playing a song. We're
playing a song. We're playing a song. We
know that. Well, why did nobody say
anything? Okay, we're going to play on
on Top of Old Smokey.
What's the beat?
Okay. What's one with a dot over it?
One. Wait, wait, wait. Ready?
Wait. It's 1135. 1135. Okay.
>> [music]
>> That just sounds like a [\h__\h] That's
just That sounds like a the bell sound
when you have to switch periods, bro.
What?
[music]
This song sucks. I'm playing it.
This song [\h__\h] sucks.
I'm playing it right. You have to go
faster. Oh, like like [music]
bro, have you ever se have you ever been
to like uh somewhere in the Caribbean
and they're playing one of those
hollowed out like it's like this, but if
you concaved it in and you play it like
and they go
like a steel pan. Yeah, that shit's
awesome. I don't think I have to play it
like that, though. Oh, wait. Okay,
ready. [clears throat]
London Bridge. London
Bridge.
London Bridge. Wait. Oh, no. It's
London. Hold up. [\h__\h] [snorts]
London
Bridge
up bars is will falling down. Wait. Oh,
no. You have to read it across. Sorry. I
was sorry.
Um, I was reading I was reading like
London Down, but it's just London Bridge
Across. I'm done with this. I'm done
with this. I'm done with this. I'm never
going to play one of these songs in in
in a good [\h__\h] way. I don't know why
the hell I'm trying to learn one of
them. Next. Now, we have a short
survival kit.
So, uh, I've seen these on Tik Tok shop
and, uh, I always thought they were
stupid as [\h__\h] but they ended up having
one on Etsy. Uh, the kit includes one
handy dandy disposable undies, one count
fresh and unused.
Uh, booty wipes to clean your ass so
fresh and clean. Brown paper bag used
for disposing your nasty ass [\h__\h]
covered underwear. and Shark survival
keychain. Proudly to show it off.
Let's get in here. These are the four
flushable wipes.
They can I I can tell they're a little
bit wet.
Uh they gave me their business and
socials. Let's throw that in the trash.
Uh I survived a shard attack keychain
and uh
some other [\h__\h] This product sucks.
Also, oh, it comes with shitty di shitty
shitty shitty shitty diapers. These
diapers suck. These diapers blow ass.
[\h__\h] terrible. This is disgusting.
This product's ass. Never buy it. The
reason I'm doing that is because there's
going to be some cockass loser that's
going to clip this and try and splice it
in a way that I'm promoting these
diapers so they can receive commission
on TikTok using my [\h__\h] likeness. So,
your [\h__\h] ass could go shove your fist
up your ass because this product sucks.
They do that all the time. If I I'll say
I'll I'll review something that I got
and then they'll take it and be like,
"Oh, promo. Buy this. Joe Bart loves
it." And then they get [\h__\h] money
because they're trying to [\h__\h] get
people to buy the product and get 20%
commission. The product sucks ass. Why
would I ever need a [\h__\h] Shark
survival kit? It's terrible. It's
terrible. What are you What are you
talking about? I understand it's a gag
gift, but it's like, "Oh, I [\h__\h] my
pants in public. You know what I'm
doing? I'm walking to the bathroom. I'm
taking my shitty poopy underwear off.
throwing them in the [\h__\h] corner of
the bathroom or in the trash can, wiping
my ass, and then I'm freeballing it
until I get home. I'm not going to put
on a diaper. I'm not going to put on a
diaper and [\h__\h] go, "Oh, luckily I
have my ready wipes with me." No, I'm
just going to [\h__\h] wipe my ass with
the one ply toilet paper they have in
the airport bathroom. This happened to
him before. It did not. It did not. I'm
just saying that's what I would do. I've
thought it through. When I go anywhere,
the first thing on my mind is, is there
somewhere I could pee? Because I have
the bladder of a uh chipmunk and
I It's not even an off course, Chad.
It's a genuine problem. If I'm going out
drinking and we go to a bar that seats,
you know, 500 people, but they have one
bathroom with two urinals,
I'm not liking that, you know, because
I'm going to slam 3, four beer, now I
have 48 ounces of liquid in my bladder
that I got to go [\h__\h] piss out and I
got to pee every 15 minutes, you know?
So, it's like that's a problem. Like, if
I I remember when I was a kid, that
would make me anxious. That was like
something that I would get anxiety over
having to [\h__\h] pee so bad that I'm
like I don't want to go somewhere where
there's not a bathroom. I think this is
it. I think this is our last product and
we saved the best for last and I'm happy
we're reviewing this product last. Chat,
you don't know what it is, but I do.
It's that pseudocience [\h__\h]
It's copper rods that electrocute you in
very small microwaves to cure cancer.
You want me to read through this this
[\h__\h] crack [\h__\h] I read this because
I needed to know how to use this for
stream. But as I was reading this, I
went, "Wow, this is for crazy people.
This is This also cost editor put the
money over there. Money should be right
here on the products. Every product for
how much I spent for the first part.
this and you know maybe factor in like
five you know $5 each product for
shipping. Anyways, so just put product
price plus shipping. Anyways, this costs
like $150 and it is no joke a D battery
in some big ass [\h__\h] box that you
hook up a red and black wire and it has
two copper rods. This was made so by
some doctor apparently. The zapper
cannot be used by the following people.
people with implanted pacemakers and
other electronic devices, pregnant and
breastfeeding women, children under six.
The Zapper has been tested on children
over six, it says. So, that's nice to
know they hooked a seven-year-old up to
this. Uh, patients suffering from
epilepsy or receiving treatment, having
undergone an organ transplant,
undergoing radiation, having prosthetics
or metal parts in your body, significant
heart problems, blah blah blah. What are
the possible side effects of using the
Zapper therapy? It's very unlikely, but
skin irritation may occur as a reaction
to the electrodes or the current itself.
In case of redness, burning, blistering,
blah blah blah, change it, consult a
doctor, you know, yap, yap, yap. Prone
to skin irritation.
Uh, some something about 100 hertz.
Okay, here we go. Regarding frequency,
the zapper is equipped with five
different selectable frequencies ranging
from 33 hertz to 250 kilhertz. How much
is that? Is that dangerous?
The low frequencies are able to
penetrate more than the high
frequencies. If we base ourselves on
right frequencies, we have different
frequencies can be useful for different
things. If you would like to cure your
asthma, get energy, have some more vigor
or wakefulness,
you should use 33 kHz on this stupid
[\h__\h] uh pseudocience machine. Uh, if
you want to fix your eyesight, headache,
sinocitis, or allergies, 344 kHz or 344
hertz. Sorry. Uh, and [clears throat]
I'm not lying when I say this. If you
would like to cure your herpes,
abdominal pain, alopecia, anemia,
hallucinations, angina, aneurysms, or
Parkinson's,
this will cure you with 5 kilhertz. And
if you have the universal frequency hold
a clarker of bodgege spectrum parasites.
So you want to get a parasite out of
your body 30 kHz. Um if you have the
flu, muscle pain, arthritis, contraure
or epicondilitis,
uh this will cure you with 250 kHz.
Uh so yeah, this is uh crazy crazy
cuckoo crazy. Cure your herpes. That's
for life.
Maybe a herpes breakout. What if it's
genital? Do you put the rods elsewhere?
Are they still in the hands? You know, I
kind of need to know more. It says wrap
it in a moist paper towel
to ensure good contact. Okay, so I have
to dip a paper towel in water and put it
on this.
Place the electrodes on your skin for
seven minutes. When they're up, pause
for 20 minutes and then repeat two more
times after you've stomped the parasites
out according or after that you've
stomped the parasites out according to
Dr. Halda Clark. [snorts] So, if I have
a a [\h__\h] parasite in my body,
I just do this for seven minutes, stop
for 20, and then do it another seven,
stop for 20, do another seven. Uh, and
then that'll get the parasite out of my
body. If you're trying to treat your
intestines, you want to put it on your
hands, your immune system, including
allergies. Uh, you put them on your feet
if you have a pancreas or kidney or
gallbladder problem. And you attach them
to your weight. What about herpes? What
do you do? What do you do with herpes?
Like that. See, that's what I
understand. Like, why are they writing
this down? This is crazy news. This is
like actually insanity.
It'll cure your alpha gal. Do you think
if I zapped myself enough?
I don't think this is even How much is
250 kHz? That's probably the the the
largest, right? Like would I feel that
because this is like such low frequency
that it's probably not really going to
do much. I have to go wet a paper towel
real quick. Do that one. Well, we'll do
different modes just to see if I even
feel it. But it's basically just a
battery hooked up to two copper rods.
Okay. So, what are we curing first?
Arthritis?
I don't remember. I gotta unwrap these.
I don't know why I squeegeeed them like
that.
Does it cure hemorrhoids? Maybe. I think
I would have to probably uh
contact Dr. Holda Clark.
She might know a little bit more. Cure
herpes. Well, I don't have herpes,
but I feel like we should just go one at
a time, you know? Oh, she's dead. Well,
I guess the uh what did she die of? Hold
Clark died in uh September 3rd of 2009
from complications of multiple mile, a
form of cancer that affects your blood
and bones. Despite claiming that all
cancers were caused by parasites
incurable via her zapper device. Oh, so
when she means parasite, she doesn't
mean stomach parasite. She says this
thing cures cancer. Okay.
Uh yeah. No. Go to a doctor.
Go to a doctor. Don't buy a $130 [\h__\h]
hold a zapper on Etsy or go to some
[\h__\h] crazy person uh that thinks
they're going to [\h__\h] fix these
problems. That means it's on.
I don't feel anything.
Should I up it?
We're curing arthritis now.
I feel a little tingle. I feel a little
tingle in my hands.
It's more of like a vibration, honestly.
We'll go one more.
We are now at five hertz.
I'm curing herpes.
If I had it, max it out. We have to go
one at a time. What if it starts
hurting?
I don't feel anything yet. It's still a
little tingly.
We're now at 30 kHz.
I feel it.
Not really. I'm lying. I don't really
feel very much. I do feel tingling, but
it's only on like the very pieces of my
skin that are touching it.
One more. It's not voltage. What is it?
Because it said it could burn your skin.
So, it has to be some sort of voltage.
It's maxed out
and it's on.
It's hertz. What is kilohertz? What is
250 kHz equivalent to? Like
getting static electricity, putting a
[\h__\h] knife in a toaster. Like, I
don't know how much that is. 250,000
hertz. But what is that? A nano vault.
Oh, so it's literally nothing.
Wait, sorry. That like made No, actually
I can't tell if it's like I'm [\h__\h]
convincing myself of this or it like it
start it made my hands like close a
little bit. It's frequency.
I feel like I feel something though.
It's definitely zapping me. Like my
hands feel more closed when I'm touching
it.
Turn it off. Dude, Dr. Holda Clark is
literally curing me of everything. I
feel it. I definitely feel it. It
doesn't feel great. You broke out the
placebo zapper. Yeah. For $135.
It's curing me of all illnesses.
But I have to do this for seven minutes.
Stop. And then do it for It does hurt.
No, it's definitely doing something.
It's definitely I kind of want to just
touch it.
doesn't really do much when you just
touch it. Okay, this product is the
biggest [\h__\h] out of all of them. Uh I
don't know why I I just get I have I
have a personal gripe with people that,
you know, believe in this [\h__\h] uh but
more so the people that shill it on
those people to make money and and
there's certain pseudociences that are
like you know maybe somewhat more
research and kind of tiptoeing the line
like chiropraxy or something where it's
like you know they are doing something
to your body but like this [\h__\h] I don't
even know if I would call it a
pseudocience this is like a scam like
there's nothing that points towards this
curing genital herpes cancers you know
this is the [\h__\h] that people fall for
and then die young because they refuse
to go to a doctor. And sure, if they had
gone to a doctor, there's still a chance
that they die, but it's like they could
have, you know, had a 40% higher chance
of living if they had [\h__\h] gone to a
doctor. Or people will do half doctor
[\h__\h] and then and then they'll it'll
come back and they'll be like, I'm going
to do pseudocience. I'm going to do
aroma therapy.
And then they [\h__\h] die, you know? So,
it's like I'm not sure how popular of a
product this is. Somebody suggested it,
but this is uh so stupid. This is so
[\h__\h] stupid. This is like the [\h__\h]
of all of them. I would never recommend
somebody to have this product or use
this product. Should I throw it out? I
mean, this was $130. I feel like at this
point I have to keep it. The shark kit
or this? Which is worse? Well, the shark
kit's just stupid and it's like trying
to be a funny gag gift like bacon
toothpaste, but it's like
it's stupid. This is like this that
doesn't harm anybody. This type of [\h__\h]
like actually gets people killed. Not
the product itself, but the fact that
people turn to the product thinking it's
actually going to [\h__\h] do something.
Aromotherapy somewhat works. Yeah. But
not in the sense of like curing cancer.
Aroma theapy is yes studied to like help
with anxiety and other certain things
but like not to the effect of like hey
you have like prostate cancer why are
you using a [\h__\h] hold a clark machine
you know? Well oh my god well we're
done. Well that was a [\h__\h] fun
review. I um I don't know. I'm not upset
with the Etsy review. It's more so like
it took a while for everything to come
in and it is individual sellers and then
also it's just like some of the products
are really cool and then some are just
so [\h__\h] stupid. But I mean that's
like the mixture of Etsy itself. But I
will say like out of everything that we
got, the only dumb [\h__\h] I mean outside
of this is like
like this is like AI like put so like
it's just like random [\h__\h] printed on a
shirt, you know? Everything else it's a
cool shirt. What do you mean? Okay,
fine. It's cool shirt. But it's like
outside of this stuff,
it really was it was better. Like I mean
the Amazon product review and Teimu had
some like cooler [\h__\h] but a lot of it
was also like slop. The only real
problem with this one like outside of
you know things being expensive and
expensive to ship was like the [\h__\h]
the ray gun breaking. But I mean that
was that that happens with every review
with at least one product. So I had fun.
I thought it was fun. I don't know what
we're going to do next. Would you guys
want to do like either Tik Tok shop or
do another Amazon one but like something
category-wise? I feel like that would be
really cool. Like an Amazon suggestion
tab thing, but like we do like five
products in like five different
categories and then rank them where it's
like this is the best of these products,
you know? If it's like five food
products, five blank, five stuff. But it
that would be if we did like Amazon
again. If we did Tik Tok shop, I could
just do Tik Tok shop. But if I did Tik
Tok shop, I wouldn't want people to just
be recommending like just only Chamoy
pickle. Chamoy pickle and like other
[\h__\h] dumb [\h__\h] freeze-dried
Skittles, the [\h__\h] Grandpa's Weer,
[\h__\h] like that. AliExpress would be
horrible, bro. AliExpress would be
unbearable to do. I don't think I would
do that. All right. Well, chat, we're
about to watch the Minecraft ARG video.
Destroying a world that doesn't exist.
This [\h__\h]
[music]
>> [music]